The cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright
Watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
We are Kangol
They spill everything right, third eye Thursday.
That's not what it is, third eye Thursday.
Yeah, we're gonna start having nicer teams here.
What's up guys, how are you?
Hey Christine, hey sweetie, hold on, let me make glasses.
I feel like I'm an old man now, officially.
I'm like Mr. Magoo, I'm like squinting,
I cannot find my fucking glasses,
and here they are, okay.
Hi guys, hey Bita.
Oh
Hi guys, hey J-Dog
Hi
Yeah
Fuck
That's everybody. I was I was interested. He's me to me. It's like I'm not I mean
It's nice to have but then he's like even when he's nice. He's like they mean everybody else. I don't know
Yeah
Really did thank you
God I'd like fuck my like my air is all clean. It's like never been this clean for a long time
Yeah, I need to have my eyes checked because I had a I had a
LASIK, you know
Yeah, so
I don't know we're a few things and I have or if you do t-shirts
Um, I got some stuff in the mail today like I got
This is a cool case for my tablet. I got
Like five bucks. I got this like silky stick. I've got a light on it
Anyway
Okay
Yeah, I mean I had it it was an interesting time earlier tonight. You know what happened to your crown you were number one
Oh, well, I don't know. I have to go check the the rankings. You might be your tide with some people
because they
Hey, beta
What happened? You know, I paid the light bill. I paid the light bills in electricity long. It's just like lights are out
Uh, I might turn on a little bit. I just was like, hey, hey, I had like Lola city right here. Tricks are sitting up here. Give us the OQ. They are, oh.
Hi, guys. Let me see Tricks on. Where are you? Tricks, where are you? There you are.
He's up here. Are you up here? You're sitting up there? Oh, hi. Hi, sir. Hi. Hi, sir.
You can say hi Lola makes the nice you make the nicest face the camera. Oh, you're okay. You turn oh
There's really really just came inside. Wow look her eyes are going
Oh
Who's that cat?
Turn your life full on that kids. Oh my gosh, my
Just colors, okay, oh turn it turn it off. Oh
Yeah, sorry
Yeah, that's yeah, she had the resting bitch the RBS she does
My my my actual like my middle my last initial are are in B, right?
So I'm
Unresting bitch
No, no, no, I'm definitely not
Well, you're just thinking about Rudy. Yeah, he just popped into the door and
Ran to the room and so I got the actual table all clean I got all my books organized
I have I do too. Do you see my do you see this picture? I mean, I think we sort of explain those pictures
Yeah, the picture it was it's on my community wall
But it's like cat GPT made this picture of me and it's like I look like the biggest like asshole
Um, but it's funny. I kind of think it's funny. So let me see if I can find it. Let me see. Um, photos
Let's see
That is a really resting base. Look, I'm like, I look like I'm in a bad mood that day
Okay, she could see and thank you for being here. I love you. Yeah, so
Tonight it was interesting, you know, because of course we had like it's like it's like D. Trump impersonator and
Then our FK was there and they were kind of funny. I don't know
They got their voice voice changers or something. They were doing some comedy and
You know, it was like, you know, not my
Believe my thing it was this political comedy. It's like, you know, it was kind of I was there kind of funny
I like the Trump like at the imitation. He did was funny like and his like
the sound of funny and just like you know, but
You know material and then the RFK. He's just like they kept they kept like like, you know
Oh, just do a terrarium do a terrarium for him and I'm like, okay. Well, I don't want to like be silly about it
I wouldn't yeah, I think you care her to pretty seriously. I don't want to do just like pull cars for like
You know fake, you know, but I saw it like this is cars for the actual person, but
Yeah, and so then they left and that and then it was like
Again, it's like a conversation was being had like conversation of being held that I did not feel I was like really
Kind of felt very after it's like I never explained it's like feeling like it's my show but it's like but almost like I feel like
Not like welcome on my own. No, it's not. I know it's not nothing. It's like, I know I do it, but
It's kind of like that feeling and it's like no one really give me I mean they say oh, where's site and then I
Don't know. I think I've seen people making fun of me all night. So that's just my securities
Oh, the Trump guy joined mine like six months ago. He couldn't take it. Yeah
Hey, it was funny for like 20 minutes and then like these are like going like, you know to try to talk about
Yeah, if he sce I and stuff and I was like and then you know, I'm like no no no no
Of course with my no no no, but uh
They get to ignore me then Alice comes on starts screaming about oh, he's gonna get it a cap, man
And it's just like uh, okay. I'll just it's just like I'll in this year. So I started it up again
Yeah, we're hanging out
Oh, I know Christine. I probably shouldn't be taken personal. I know but they get quite do you get quite quite personal?
It's like it's almost seems like you know, I just like I have this little I
Don't know
Think there people are calling it something else
But uh, like you know, it's a couple dog whistles or something like that
But it's like I've been trained on dog whistles by a Russian. So I know like all the I know all the I know all the I know
Please I think it's passing
Alice knows things won't hang down. I know he just he screams about it and then it's like I just thought I was like
Okay, let me just reset the energy. So I did and then
And then people are like, oh, why'd you do this? And then like stasks on the coming on like this like he really annoying
And so I'm like, you know, I
Don't know. Sorry, and some people will be annoying, but it's like, you know, I don't get triggered
He has like
One thing I can't take a smug. I really audience love the Trump guy
Yeah, I mean I think he was funny and I don't know why they I think it kept having to kick off the RFK person
Because he was like saying more extreme language
But the Trump guy was fine. He was I could deal with Trump. I can hang out with Trump
I don't know if I could build RFK
I did do some, I did do some readings, but it's like, no, it's just like, I get a, so
let's, let's, let's do, over these, we did some great readings yesterday. It says to
like, start incorporating the cards more, you know, I got recommended. Hey, Sean
James, you did your future wife. Well, congratulations. I think this was, I have a
I think I made this one, I just made this one with AI too, hold on, that's fine, that was like that a little bit, no I'm not, I mean it's like I'm not like, I don't even know what it really means, I just, it's like too complicated for me, I don't understand politics really, I just like a more
Not interested unless it's like, you know, I don't like what I'm hearing right now
I might not can't even discuss that like, you know, what they're saying. It's like all the initials are a
You know I'm talking about and it's like it's like I think Florida or something and it's like
kind of like I
Don't know what are they doing? What are they doing now?
And it's like oh and then it's like people some people are going to say oh well those people that they probably deserve it
Like there's something it's like you imagine it's like especially
There's just all these nuts out there, you know the better country conspiracies
But who knows researching what one night and it's like you know
They stumble upon the actual conspiracy that is being monitored by the government or something and
They know too much or something or they or they figure out something like I don't know what what reason could they have to be taking these people out
To this place without notifying
relatives without
You want to link okay, but how are they doing this? Like or why it's like, you know, I want to know more because I know you know
We know it's like one G U a and T a and a mo which they've batched it whatever one, but we know that how here's really right there
Yeah, clean my house is like it's all clean
Mr. Roos
Anyway, okay. Yeah, so I don't know if anyone knows anything about it. I'm I don't know if it's conspiracy
I just I'm actually like videos about it now like mm-hmm. It's well here
Why is that rhetorical like well really it's like we have these press like a pressing need for an extra kind of I
Just don't get it
Good morning. Hi, sweetie. Yes, it looks good. Good job. Good job. Good job. Thank you. I
try to maintain it every day. I know it's hard work for men to do that, but I think women have
like a little bit more OCD. So yeah, I was like a little bit backed up on my laundry and blah,
Well, there's people that like that couple that came over like they clean my like or he clean my bathroom one night
And he like it was like so clean
It was like my bath was like a different color like it was just like you know
It was so good and then like and then but that you know, and then it was kind of kind of like let's it have
Beautifully clean like they're clean the floor perfectly
But it's all the trash all over and so it was like I finally like cleaned everything off of it
Most conspiracy comes to truth often they do and but sometimes it's their pit out there as
red hairys or like decoys like or like or even also to make people look crazy
sometimes but some of them I believe are very true.
Who are you talking? What are you talking about?
Oh, Christina is saying, most conspiracies come to truth.
I'm sorry, it runs like, like, in the chat.
I don't know why, I just, I was like,
I didn't even read the chat, I'm like,
what, red hair, orange hair, what?
Red herring, it's like, when you would like,
it's like a little, like a little distraction.
I was like, I thought you were talking about like a ginger guy.
Yeah, red herring, yeah.
Well, you know, gingers don't have stoles, you know.
So people are crazy, you know, Christina and,
You know it's getting scary and scary. Also there are people also something called cuckoo for cocoa puffs where they're just like
I don't even know what they're thinking. I mean if people are just they're doing this crazy shit. It's like what?
It's like everyone. I know it seems to be some kind of major criminal
I don't know. I mean no wonder was looking at you know
FBI's
Been watching this fucking youtube. It's crazy
Everyone's just out doing all kinds of shit
Right. Crazy. I think there's going to be a lot more.
Sean, you're funny. The only reason I made that bet was because Salman said if I don't drink for 30 days, he goes, he goes, I challenge you not to drink for 30 days.
I said, I challenge you not to cover. Hi, Rudy. Hi, QT.
I said fine. I'll make a deal with you. You don't cover me for three thirty days because I know
Content is like my content. So I won't drink for 30 days. So it's a bet. Yep. Is it going good?
Well, yeah, I mean like I can do whatever the hell I want but oh, I know you can I know you can't but it's like
I mean, I said I wasn't gonna drink for 30 days on my birthday and then I like I like I
Modified it to uh, no, no, no, no hard alcohol except for my birthday
I don't know if I love the hard alcohol my birthday, but I just drink beer that month, you know, and otherwise and then
No, I'm not really drinking hard alcohol much. Sometimes I have a drink out, but uh
I mainly have like today, for example, I'm going to drink this right now, but I haven't had eaten a drink today.
Like yesterday.
Yeah, I mean, I can go without drinking easily.
It's just like when you do panels and you get all these like different people up there that are super drunk.
You just kind of like can't tolerate them unless you're drinking with them.
You know what I mean?
But um, yeah, when he gets crazy, but yeah, I can go.
I used to never drink. I started drinking I think like less than a year ago when I started doing the streams
I didn't drink like for years before that. I never was a drinker
You know as I like I mean I would drink at dinner like family dinners and stuff like and that would be fun to get drunk
But then it's like I never felt like getting drunk otherwise. I would just like like to like be sober and like you know
When I was young though, when I was like in my 20s, yeah drink a lot like one of clubs and stuff like that
but then
When I was like between my hooves like 30 early 30s to like almost late 40s
I'd never drink like I didn't for years and years
I just couldn't even like stand the taste of alcohol, but then I don't know
I don't know, but I don't drink hard liquor just like champagne
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I like a prosecco and like champagne and
Occasionally tequila maybe that's like the only thing I'll even drink like you know
Yeah, I can I like a good margarita like a cat like margarita. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Yeah
For you by the way, I'm kind of what a
wife a wife
You yes, yes
So if I was somebody like a terror card reader, you probably know her because she's like pretty like, I don't know, she's pretty big, but I mean, you know, compared to like, you know, other streamers or whatever.
And I was like, oh my God, he's perfect for psyche. She is, she is.
No, she's gorgeous gorgeous gorgeous like beautiful
Oh, she's more Russian
Yeah, I'm gay. It's that's never gonna work. I think she'll turn you straight
I'm gonna put in the back chat. You can check out our channel. Okay
You have the margaritaville missy
Yeah, we're missing the margaritaville song
I think uh, I feel like I'm wasted away in Margaritaville. I said it like Middle East
If you go look at it or tell me what you think you think it's just pretty okay, let me have a look
It was really trippy because I was like just like somebody was vertical and I went up and then I just ran into her
I was like, oh, I wonder if psyche knows about her. Oh
She's gorgeous, but you know, but you know what she looks like a lot
She's like Rose McGowan or like some kind of like. Oh, yeah, she's gorgeous. She's beautiful
I got them, but uh, yeah, you know, you know, like I like that kind of type that's sucky busy type
And she's cool, she's kind of badass, you know, yeah
And I was watching she had like 200 people watching yesterday. So check her out and maybe you cannot interact with her
Yeah, I just subscribed and uh, I'm cool. You know, thank you for like that. I mean, uh, like I don't know
Are you looking for a man or you're looking for like a guy?
No, no, I found this guy his name is mr. Bigpipes. Are you interested in?
Yeah
You know, wrap a pipe around my skin.
Yeah, yeah, OK.
OK.
I was just wondering, you know, he looks like he can do it too.
Or how about good times?
Have you met this guy named Good Times?
He seems to be a nice guy.
No, I haven't known Good Times for a long time, too, no.
Well, he seems like he was, well, he was, he was, he was kind of like,
wasn't he kind of like trying to play the smooth?
He was like starting to be really cool the other night in front of Paige, you know
Yeah, yeah, he was like, hey, he was just like so confident and he was just like so smiling and like I was like, oh my gosh
I like I like them on that actually I would rather turn lesbian and
Get back with my ex who annoys that a lot of me
Then to ever never ever I never know I'm very picky
I don't think that I don't think it's safe to debilitate people especially on YouTube
I mean it's like it's a date that gets people to vent on I mean let's we like people fell in love like really
I don't know it's like some some of the people like I all of a sudden I see their their uh, you know
Their criminal records are to pop up
It's like well these people have
Seven words. I don't know that's a horrible thing. No, you know, of course, you know, they did not really that bad or else
He'd be you know, they'd be in a
I
There's a couple of people that are really really nice in the community a couple of like men, but the red like most of them are douchebags
You know
They're usually I mean, but no, I mean in real life. Um, I
Get head on but I'm just like I don't think I'm in the mood for any but I'm just kind of I'm over it
Who knows? Yeah, I'm working pre-manipausal or a pteromonopausal or whatever they call it. I'm not in the mood for no fucking man
I just like
That like you know Joker was like real nice to me
And he was like real cool like super nice
And then he like to kind of like this kind now he's a kind of like means to me again like it's like
Yeah, I mean it sounds like he's really mean he's just like sarcastic and like you know, I don't know
But it's like that's why I don't I try not to like like people anymore like perfect because it's like
He's very he's very young and immature, you know, so he's kind of like
Yeah, he jokes around but he's a sweetheart. He's a good guy
Casey is completely turned on me
You know, he's evil. Don't worry about him. You know, Casey. I mean like a lot of it like a lot of you
You know, I don't know some people like also
The mill some still come and go
Well, I know you got all these male sums around you, you know, I do well, it's like, you know, I don't know it's a
every guy is like
Like I thought came out of dry. I was like, oh, he's a stimp and now he's like he thinks he's not he'd be he like he acts like he's like the fucking
Hey, Canadian mafia or something. I don't know. He's like, yeah
Watch collection, you know, you know, yeah, I know I know I know
I like it too, but then he's like he's like he's like tries to like and then yesterday
I kept looking at my thumbnail on my show just like a second have these look on YouTube and stuff going back and forth
And it's like and then he was on with
somebody he was like talking to like
Alex, he's talking to somebody and then he was like
And he is sick or something his mouth is like he's like so smocked
Yeah, I was like why is it why is he so smocked and he's just like oh, well, don't you know that you know
The watch is what these these men these most important men in the world
you know these
they'll look at his watches, you know and
Say they look at you have a nice watch and if you don't then they but they judge you on it
And I'm like, okay. Well, yeah, my dad was in business. He had like a lot of watch and he loved watches and stuff
but I never like got back and I was like, well, you know, but
Also like a lot of millionaires or even like they will wear fake jewelry like fake fake stuff and not
In case they you know because they've probably been robbed before a lot of loose stuff and something
And so he's like, oh, well, dude, we'd never wear it. They would never wear it. They'd go and then he's like, I would know I would know
And then I was like, how would you know this by looking at it like this?
It was being a watch expert. Yeah
Only went to get his whole watch Joe and then I think I say because an expert of everything apparently
Sigg is the one like sick is really annoying like sometimes he'll just go on rants and rants and rants
And you're just like everybody else is talking and he's reading the chat and he's answering like is this panel is a lot
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I mean it's very annoying and then they kept having a money like
Thank you
I know I told you I don't like you but that doesn't mean I'm not trying to
Help you. He's like I like he's like I'm trying to you know get get karma by being nice to a gay person
Or I don't know. He's just saying this nonsense. Oh my god. My hair is all matted. That's right here. What happened here? Yeah
I have like a bucket. I look at this hair. My hair is like completely like a knot right there
How did that happen? It's like remember that one cartoon ever not cartoon. It was like that little kid with the
I don't know it's like it's like what it's like really it's like a braid it feels like a braid this is
It's weird. How'd that happen? I don't know
Can you get karma that way? I don't know like some people think, you know, there's an episode of South Park where I think
You know everyone like I guess Cartman like eats all the skin off the Kentucky fried chicken and so they're all mad at him
They're like let's just pretend and work. We don't even see him like he's dead to us
And if he's a ghost and so they just pretend like they don't see him
And so he thinks he's like dead and then like and then but then butters can see him and so he thinks butters can
see him
But yeah, he's like butterscouts and he has to give fruit baskets around the neighborhood and he can make it
But for all his negative shit, and they can go to heaven or something and he sings a song. I'm gonna make make it
It's a good episode. Yeah, we yeah, I love South Park, you know every episode
so make make it right yeah so yeah that's a good way I don't think it being
nice to a gay person is a good way to get karma maybe being nice to me you'll
get so hopefully I hope you do you know but like you know I don't know I don't
think it's just
I'm like, I'm like some kind of like charity case of karma or something. I don't know. Maybe I am
That's stupid it doesn't for me it doesn't matter what you are or who you are
It's like you can be a good person to whoever that you like and whoever you respect
Do you know what I mean? I don't give a shit about like if you're gay straight
You could be straight most of the people I've met are fucking straight assholes and they're straight assholes
Gay people are nice. My best friend is gay like Michael is like he's always nice to me. He's a sweetheart
Hi, how are you a cat? I always call you a cat. Hi, Rumi. How are you doing? No, I'm just in I'm just in
That's just Ian. Oh my god. Oh my god. Thank you friend. Big miss. Mix up. How are you?
Is it can I just tell you something I want to just one second and I'll get off beat I promise you
You can stay as long as you want. I can leave if you want. No, don't I don't want you to leave
I'm just
Oh, you're messing with me. Okay. All right. I just want to just tell you I'm very sorry about
My feeling that you get from me when I was in your chat room. Oh
You're nice, I know you are no you're you're you're a very nice positive person
I like you know, and you sit, you know, you you know, you said, you know for Goddy and
I guess for Ziggy and JT and that was good, you know, it's like you're a nice
Nice friend and you're friendly. I had no problem with you
You know, I don't feel like I just I just wanted you to know that I am a very fun person and me and Stevie I
Hate her fucking racism and I hate that bitch because she has got to be the worst person for racism
I've ever met in my old morning
Call me
So that's why
Said terrible words about me because I I rejected him
most of the rejected you that have beta the guy named Vader
I rejected
Justine is one of the funniest characters of female characters I've ever seen on any panel.
Best name?
I'm Tony.
Is Vader your master?
Vader?
No, I hate Vader with a passion.
Because I can use a little bit.
Dear father.
No, I rejected Vader.
I didn't want to hurt me because I I I I I did not want to have to have anything to do with him in a relationship way.
Open wide, Justine. Open wide.
Okay, I'm going to go now because I'm not Justine.
Don't leave us. Okay. All right. I won't. Yay
Okay
Christine Christine one thing about the psyche versus I
We I
Devils rejects or something. I know that's already a movie, but and we're not that crazy, but
Rejected even my state morning
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, what else can you do but become, yeah, let's see. I think I'm just like, basically,
obviously I have stuff on earth and that's like, it's fucking unfortunate, but it's a slime.
Okay, so let me see. Jesse is a master of karaoke. Oh, that's good. Interesting. I am going to do that.
What is that? What is karaoke? It's like, it's like, when you sing along to like the instrumental.
No, okay, karaoke. Okay. Yeah, yeah, she said it the right way
You think I was like it I get this I got like a food
I have a learning disability. Oh, no, no
Yeah, I'm dyslexic and I've got ADHD really bad. Okay. Yeah, you're just like me. Okay. Okay. You're I'm the same way
Okay. Well, I
I think I'm dyslexic to have ADHD too
I mean, I've never been diagnosed, but I think I do.
Can I ask you a question?
Did you paint all those pictures yourself, thank you, Dad?
Are you an artist?
Oh, I'm talking about the graphic art, the graphic design?
Or what are you talking about?
I'm always, it's, you know, it's Canva,
and so it's like, Canva is like really,
like has a lot of templates,
it has a lot of,
It's really easier than Photoshop to use, I'd say,
plus it has some AI stuff,
so you can bring up exactly what you want
and stuff like that.
And then it's like,
I think when you work with the machine together,
it can be really powerful results.
And so, of course, with the AI songs and the fucking AR,
I mean, I wish I could draw like that, right?
But I can come up with good concepts
and that counts for some things too, right?
You know sometimes you just you know what you have to do like when I paint and stuff that I do
What I mean, who is that what I have to go for a walk
I go for a walk and I unblock my mind and I don't take my this I don't take my phone or anything
I just go for a walk around the block and that usually you have a dog
Tommy who's that woman in your picture in your picture that you're that somebody that approves of you using that picture and everything
Oh, yeah, it's a public. It's a famous person public figure
Are you you see you like this woman or what what's going on?
I mean, it's just a foreign star. I don't think it matters. I just think it's a funny picture
Are you scared?
Well, she's not that woman.
No, she's not that who's that woman that Mr. Big Pies work for?
That's his.
Oh, no, Alexandria Myers.
Is that her?
There you go.
Is it her yep, you're correct. Oh my god. Okay. Well, I don't want I don't want her picture on my show because you know why
I live with her for a month. I live with her and I'm for a fucking month
Does he approve you using her picture?
She's a porn star. She's a porn star in a public figure pictures everywhere
Well, I don't know. I heard she like it. She goes after channels and stuff. I've heard people
Because you're afraid of her. I'll take it off. But like she's
She's not an imbd page so if she can't deal with her picture on an avatar that might be pretty sad, but
Yeah
Another point I wanted to get across to you because somebody says that I'm homophobic and I'm absolutely
Not homophobic. I have been in for pride parade. No even more and I'm thinking about it
I've been in
I've been basically involved with the pride parade bump is a spectator and in
since fucking
So, yeah, and I have been fighting for your guys' right to party.
Right.
Here at LGVD, Al, but why do people have the wrong idea about that?
I don't understand.
Those are reasons why people were saying you were...
Well, do you want to know why people are getting pissed off?
is because of the pronouns, because the original core message of the gay and lesbian and trans
people was that they didn't want to be separated from the world, they wanted to be integrated,
so when you put pronouns on something, you automatically remove them from society because
And when I went to the priperies all those years ago, they wanted to get rid of the other, and they wanted to be joined together like normal people, getting married, having babies, white pickets dancing it.
And that's not it.
Justine, are you bisexual?
Not at all, babe. I love mental straight up.
You like guys?
What happened was that I joined the Liberal Party of Canada
and nobody in my writing and the other writings
and around this neighborhood would even go to a pride parade
but because I've always stand up for the pride people
even when I was a little kid in high school.
I've always stood up for pride people Tommy also Tommy also fought for the gay gay rights
I mean
My birthday is in June 27 1987. Go look up the
Historical
So so long so long or something or so long or no, what is it?
Big pride thing or whatever
Okay
The music, the bass, the music, and if I love electronic music, that's my favorite.
So I was able to dance down the street, and I partied, because I did it in Vancouver.
I partied with my minister of defense, and I partied with Justin twice, and Justin Trudeau,
Justin Trudeau.
Just in that just entered out five times. What's he in black? Is he ever in black before he
Ran before he right when he was running
Running that the second election. I I worked my balls off for you
I didn't throw the third election because by that time I started hating Justin through though
You know that old saying power corrupts, but yeah
Absolutely
But I do want to say like, you know, I might be considered like one of the most homophobic people on the panel and definitely would consider homophobic for the gay community and that's just homophobic just because I don't have to dislike or fear gay people.
Okay, right. But it's like.
Homophobic as in I was I was a lot of gay people are like this or especially the older ones like the older generation
They don't want to be part of this regular society. They were happy being on the outside
Because they were even if they were like
Exactly.
When I say that they want to be treated normal and all sorts of things, because I know I've
talked to a lot of them and I ain't saying them and us, because I think that they're
all us.
But anyways, them, because of this, that and the other four, you know, as an example, they, they always tell me that they don't like any kind of like putting up with the back in the day stuff.
They want, they don't like to have, they don't like to have any differentiating between
Normal person and a gay person. Well, I don't know what you're saying normal and a gay person
So you can say between straight people and gay people because I think both are both are normal
Having baby having a family and why the gays can do that too gays can do that too
A dog and get married at two two thousand and six
Gaze and Canada got completely emancipated and in the States you guys are kind of emancipated
but we jumped the gun and we are allowed to have Gaze in the military in 98.
Yeah I mean it's very progressive. It is, I mean it's progressive.
You do well, I gotta go to the store to get cigarettes. I'll be back guys. Thank you for having me on
You know, see you in a little by Tommy. Have a good day
Yep. Thanks guys. I'm really cool. You. Bye
Yeah
Here I'm gonna go now
I just popped up here to say that I just hope that you don't get the wrong impression the people that I
Would get mad at me is because I when I when I block somebody I don't really ever unblock them
I hear you. Well, yeah, you're you're loyal or you're loyal and you like I am
I'm up to a point if they're gonna start shagging around with me. I don't want anything to do with them either
Cool
You too love talking to you come back soon
Yeah
And then I made this one.
Well, this is yesterday was the wild car Wednesday.
So I know I've gotten.
Who is that?
I said I made the Joker space.
I said Joker, the Joker spaces.
So that's kind of kind of Joker.
And then today is like the third I Thursday.
So I made that one.
Pretty, huh?
Are my kids cool?
And it's just the third I Thursday.
Yes.
Third I Thursday.
I don't and then I have like if you look at the description of the show
I don't know if you guys can see it but it says like a little a little blurb in there
So, you know, I'm trying to like I'm also want to do more
Incorporating the tarot into like, you know, I'll say if people are having a fight, okay
I'll be like, you know, sometimes it's hard to interrupt or like, you know after
They're coming. Hey, you guys want a car to see how you did energy looks for your relationship or I'll just always do it
Like, you know, I can pull the cars for that kind of stuff, too
It would be interesting to see like just what's the energy on this so we can do all kinds of readings
We also do like I'm gonna start doing like a
a reading, opening a show, like a show reading.
Why are these people so nosy about me drinking like I got a DUI or something?
I've never been arrested. I can drink if I want to, but no, I'm not drinking. It's 5.15 a.m. here.
in California. Uh, no, but, um, I'm not under any kind of, uh, what do you call it? Restrictions?
I don't have any reason. I just, I just wanted to make a bet. It's a challenge.
The chat is very judgmental, and it's like, it's like, what? Wait, wait, wait. I mean, I'm not all,
not all the chat is judgmental, but some of the chat is judgmental. No, I don't think all of them are.
I'm just making it up. No, no, no. Yeah, I know, but it's like, some of it, like, really, like,
the act of like I got a DUI or have my kids taken away and now after like you know urinary analysis
like this or something like I'll drink I'll drink like I think you're done like with somebody
and they were like oh be that can you not drink for 30 days I said can you not cover me for 30
days just seeing if it can happen or not because yeah
I'm pretty you know when I drink then I'll just like act buck well then crazy then they won't have any content
But I can do I can get crazy without drinking true. Trust me. Trust me. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Well, yeah, me too
You know, it's like I've been plenty crazy without any alcohol, but um, you know, I'm slowing down a little bit on the alcohol
but uh
You know
So that's a man if you can get 30 days. So yeah, but you know, I just like, you know, people were saying, oh, oh
They're like, oh Paige, you know, you're sitting in your car
Like you're she was like she's just sitting in her car
It's like people are just like like trying to like say that she's there and then like I say they're like, oh
I say it was and I don't I don't know when it was happening with him and the dog
I was kind of watching wasn't hitting his dog, but it's like people are like, oh my god
He's hitting his dog and and I say and there's like and he's saying bad things about Indian people and he
All right, so there's someone in the chat today that was like, what are you saying about Indians?
Like, I heard you're trashing Indians on your show and they're like, you guys are you're bad,
you're bad. And it's like, no one said anything bad about Indians. All page did say that many
Indians come in and hit on her on her show. I mean, that's not talking bad about Indians. They're just
hitting on her. Okay. I mean, India. Come on. Don't be embarrassed. India. Okay. Not American Indians.
Not first nation like page, but you know, I think every nationality hits on page
Yeah, I've seen it. I mean it's like but I've seen like guys that are like really like can I like they're like
Hard to be so tough and then they're like, oh, hey
It's like, oh, it's like, oh my gosh
What happened like that's a woman do to men's it is turn them into stuff. He's a little like
mushy
And they're like, and they're like really creepy and Mr. Big Five is always like hey, he's gonna take you a song and she's like no
Yeah, most of the guys in this community, they go through like every, they send for every
woman and they get like a, you know, a new fresh air, a beautiful woman that comes in
and it's like, they all, it's like mating season or something.
All the birds are like, yeah, I know these guys.
I hopefully, but hopefully they all find someone they, they like, yeah, maybe not, not, not
Yeah, I know you because you know Doug Doug you don't deserve a nice woman either. Yes, you guys should just go gay
Women are too good for you guys
Hey, you're on Jimmy's last night and there was no hold on. I never said that you hit on me
I never have I did I even say anybody hit on me the fuck this guy and some of these like
I mean
I don't even know if they come up with their own imagination.
They think you're talking to them or something, in particular.
Well, I mean, it doesn't have to people are,
I mean, that's part of the gaslighting.
It's all like on the panel of people
that join the panels and that kind of stuff
when they're on the panel.
I don't think I've ever seen Holden my cock ever take a link
or if he has no idea.
No, I've seen people overreact and think that people are talking about that and sometimes people do personalize stuff
But I think that there are stuff that there is also like ambience at like something called ambience abuse
Which is just like just words in the air meant to like meant to
Her figure or something like that. I had a nice mom and already gives me
Illusion more like it's like it's like
It's gas lady. It's a gas lady thing or it's like, oh, well, it's like, yeah, we're just we're just talking about something else
But it's like then they're like, oh, you know, they make us like look at you like
Hold on, I'm sorry, hold on right. I don't like to, I said it was holding my cock. I don't like to open the door for fucking strangers, but when they come to my house like three times within the three minutes.
The third time I'm going to be chasing their fucking ass down. I live like in a pretty safe community. And I was also online. So I was like on camera.
It was, I was being a vigilante, but I was drinking, but at the same time, I'm not scared of, you know, freaking standing up for my fight or flight just fucking went on and I'm good.
I got, in fact, I got shit fucking handled really good right now.
And I found out I found out I got everything that I needed from that person.
Yeah.
Black art. Black art. I'm sure she did not call Ivana the N word. Vita does not call people that word. Come on.
No, I don't think you, I don't think Black RG is talking about me.
Oh, okay. I'm sorry.
Drinking vigilante, holding it on Vita, holding my cock. Yeah. How come you have loads of stuff but no content?
I don't know why Holden never thought that I was even talking about him. I don't even know who Holden is.
I don't think this is a real name.
I don't know.
It sounds like one of those fake names.
And then it says, now that you gotta get kidnapped
and then you gotta chase the car.
That's how you're gonna get kidnapped
and then you can chase them to the car, okay?
Well, I don't know what you got to talk about in chat,
but, you know, hopefully you never have to come down
to that, just some running shoes, guys.
I'm not Yvonne Split.
Can I honest abana split there's so many names abana split
Ivana kiss you abana punch you. I think Ivana is talking to uh, what's her name?
Justine
I once met a vana bandersuit. I've never heard of that name and then there's what there's also what
A band or pump rules, but that's like band, you know band not abana. I guess
Then there's a vana trump, right? I'll go wherever you want. Yeah
Whoever you want
The chat is having their own little for like you and then here comes here comes. What's his name war dog?
As war dog in there too. Oh my gosh. Wow
Too late is war dog
Yeah
I don't know
Okay. So, what was I going to show you? Oh, yeah. I actually made a new thing. I made a new graphics for, yeah.
You made a new thing?
Yeah. I mean, it's just basically, you know.
Oh, is there one? There's good.
Oh.
I got that one. Yeah, I got that one. And I got...
We have a link number. Yeah, you can have a link just in here.
Freak off Fridays.
Freak off Friday. I don't think Friday is called fish taco Friday.
No, I forgot what it's called.
No, I have to like look it.
I have to look. I've written them down.
I have them written down some place.
Okay. Let me look at the.
Okay, so I need to go put this in my streamer real quick and then.
It's like I mean it's not like that great. It's if you I was trying to make this video
I was trying to put the AI stuff to video and I could only find like you know
You have to pay for it like every place and then I couldn't do it. Otherwise. There was just to I'm not that good
Hey black Archie, how did you deal with that fucking piece of shit asshole fucking J-Dog that guy's a fucking pest
What? Who is Dougie? Who is Doug D? I've never heard a Doug D in my life
And for him to say that I'm racist when I have
He's racist. No, he's racist
I understand something to me. I have worked my ass off
So that people would treat people with respect.
There's two of these.
I can't say that.
Sorry.
I'm just putting in my picture.
I'll show you.
Yeah, I'm a, I'm a really homophobic person.
for fucking years for gay people to have their rights
to party and do whatever they want.
Oh yeah, I'm really fucking gay a phobic.
And I just don't have a core of people I meet
at the gay pride parade.
And we have the best time in our lives.
Oh yeah, I'm really, really, really phobic.
I don't think you are.
I think, I think, okay, will you not take this the wrong way?
Um, when you, when you come and you're like, I did this and that for the gay people, it's almost like you're, you're being discriminative. Like, you could just be like, Hey, I'm here to chill with you.
Let's go. Hold on. Hold on. You could just I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
I'm telling you you could just be like, hey, I'm here to chill with you psyche because I like you I like your channel
You know what I mean? So I'm not saying that you are but it comes across that way when you say
Right of people to party
How can a person be accused of being
i'm not accusing i was just telling you i was saying how it can even how can anybody
even have that connotation in their head when i go and i fight for the good fight so that means
that if i never fought for their right to party and i never fought for any of their
okay i'll give you an example i'll give you an example right so that means so that means that
You're not racist, but that's a game at them.
Maybe I told you you might get offended, but I don't mean to offend you, but it's like let's say I'm Asian, right?
And then you come up here, you're like, yeah, I really like, you know, I've, you know, fought for the Asian, like, you know, so it's like, you are kind of being discriminative because just look at me as a human.
You know what I mean?
I think I got her mad.
I told her, what do you mean to offend her?
I know.
It's like when someone says, oh, well, I have, I have.
So many friends that are black. My best friend is black
What she said I thought for you guys to party everyone
Party, you know, I know that is a good car
I mean, I actually like I like that cause but I don't think we ever had a problem necessarily
Yeah, party harder than everybody else. Yeah, you can't stop the gaze from like party and the gaze are gonna figure out a way to party
Yeah, but you know what
I think but she is I think she is innocent and that she doesn't mean any harm any harm
It's like that's not offensive at all or anything, you know, it's like but it is like, you know
Some people will say oh, yeah, or they'll just think they'll still just notice that about her
Then they'll try to pick on her about that or something like that, but it's not it's nothing
it's uh i don't mind people saying anything they want about gays as long as you know we have the
same legal rights you know so and i wasn't even for marriage i don't want to get married to a guy
i don't i don't want to get married to a woman woman or a man i just want to be uh if i want to
enter a contract with somebody you know i'll go into a business but not a fucking um you know
Marriage where it's like we're like having sex and stuff. I mean, it's too strange. Then I would be worried
I don't know. I can't I can't try I don't trust men. I
Mean I don't trust myself but not teach not men
They're like they're like they're like nowadays. They're like women. I mean, it's
Not in a bad way. I'm saying like how they like to be kind of socialized like like that now
It's like they're kind of like they're bad because the mouth is any
Bigger mouth than anybody's ever been accused of having these guys are just like
Yeah, hopefully
You'll find like a lover and a soulmate
And somebody that you just is loyal to you and you're loyal to them, you know, you have like some kind of connection, but I really think why is like the whole purpose of marriage is like to, I guess it's like the organized institution to procreate and have like a family like I don't know.
At this point, I don't want to get married ever.
Right, I'm never gonna have kids and I never if you do plan having kids
I think if you do have plan I'm planning people do have plan having kids is better to be married because of course
It's like a stable
Yeah, because confusing and confusing enough with same-sex parents to them to have like them not get along
You know, but then it's hard for it's hard for like two men and two women to get along sometimes
You know, it's like it's like I mean it's hard for the opposite sex to get along
But they're so different in the first place like or in a certain way that it's like it's like almost like normal
That's expected the difference is like kind of wait hold on justine. Why do you say that like?
Like come on don't say you're not gonna come back. It's just it's what you call a debate and then some of the people in the chat
They tease they tease me too. They say things to me and I defend myself like
Don't be it. You're okay. Yeah
And I think you know, I don't know if she's like it's a Trump or whatever
I mean, it's like, you know, it's like it's kind of someone's similar to I don't know if she's like
You know, it just seems like she has kind of a little bit of that Trumpish thing. So here's my new banner. There we go
Let me see. Oh, you can't see it.
Okay, let me see.
I can fix it.
I'll fix it.
Okay.
And then, what about the chat?
Like, how much to kick somebody out of the chat?
You need to put that in the chat.
Yeah, I'll add that.
I guess I have to move that.
Moves that are the white text a little bit
Yeah
I think that that'd be the best thing that's like I think you know it's a it was really fun that night
It's really of course. It was really great when it's been funny when people are doing the financial trolling
But it's like at the end of the day. It's like, I know I was thinking about changing the prices for stuff
And I know but I was like I'll just make it just a simple thing and it's like, you know
Yeah, sure
the cloud. It looks like a fluffy cat. I don't know if you see it or not, but it kind of looks like the Persian map, but it looks like a fluffy cat with a tail to the right.
It's Rudy.
Oh
Look at the little face
How did you do that I don't know it's a game like that is magic it's just it's like the uh, the magic there we go
Oh, there I am again. See that's my little goat avatar. I made a little I mean that was a
Of course page. I just saw her in the chat. She was
Yeah, she was she was my chat earlier and
You know, she was doing there's a good readings for everybody. I was just like
No, I just thought in the chat. I wish you would
Don't see her anymore
It's been a while ago.
Hey buddy, growing on kick is an easy book.
Oh yeah, so I'm streaming on kick right now.
If you guys too, you might see some weird messages from kick.
I haven't really, I think I got like 100 views on Rumble.
That's like pretty good because I think like Chris K was
saying yeah, like 20 views or something on Rumble or something.
Or maybe I'd say it's he met on whatever.
He eventually, I don't even know his streaming service,
but, or, here's Teji.
She's here?
Yeah, she's here.
Hold on one second.
Okay.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
I came to your chat. I was like, I woke up. I, because I went to sleep early and then all of a sudden like fucking butt ass in the morning for I woke up and I was like, uh, except the kiddies early, and then I saw you were alive.
I came in there. I just wanted to say hi, but
You know, I was in a mood to freaking watch Alex, like just banter at me and I wanted a reading where it's like good energy. So that's why I told you, like, not right now, but I always love you. And I love your reading anyways. And it was really nice, but I just, you know what I mean?
Oh, I totally get it. Yeah. Yeah.
And I love you and respect you and always appreciate you.
So I just don't want you to have like a misunderstanding with what happened.
I'll just now I'm going to be fucking Alex with his bullshit while you're doing nice
readings for everybody. So I come in there and say hi and he just starts with me and I just
didn't want the energy there. Like, yeah, I was a little annoyed by him.
Oh my god, he's not what you want to have coffee to
Start with me, too. I was like, oh, I think I think I think I'm pretty good at like, you know
Pretty prompts for the yeah, so you're not talented. You're not talented. Oh, you suck
I mean, he's coming on screaming. I'm like, okay. Well, I know I'm not like I said, I know I'm not like
You know, you know wonderful musician or anything saying I know how to like talk to the AI
That's the thing to do
I'm not saying I'm special to say I'm getting the results that I'm looking for out of AI so
I don't know if he was screaming at me like I'm like you know freaking like trying this day. I'm like
Okay, I'm nothing Alex anything. Oh, and then he won't like listen to me if I tell him to turn on his microphone
He won't he'll tell me no
I can't take it anymore, and then it's like I literally have to kick him off like ten times a night or more
And it's like and then half the time I have to in the show because he says something
too much
Yeah
So J-dog is fighting with Tommy and Black RG and then two ladies over there fighting
with Black RG that Ivana is fighting, not fighting though, you know, arguing with Justine
And I don't know
We need more we need more referee we are mods in the chat, you know
Gosh
I was like I look I like like seriously I looked away from my computer for like five minutes or like my my mother like five minutes
I came back. There's like a hundred fucking um
Like a hundred chats like a hundred like a hundred comments again. It's like a few minutes over here. Tommy Jesus back home
Oh, excuse you
Tommy's like
J-dog, I'm wait. I got you on J-dog
Easy work
So let him come up and
Let's set him straight beta. He don't he ain't been around very long apparently. He don't know. He don't know some things
Fuck man, what a nice morning
Let me see if I have
Oh
Here we go
Yeah, I'm down to my end of my vape and a little bit of weed
Oh my gosh, yeah, amazing. That's why my nails are aren't dirty already. No, they're quite clean
Washington night because they're good. I think
I didn't I got I got a whole fucking like little nail kit. It's really cool
I got it from like a team. Oh, it's like all this like stuff in it
I mean it's half of them are on the table right now, but they're a big kid
those spray burs and stuff so
Thank you guys. You sent me straight for no needles that I don't I don't have needles. I don't I don't
He meant you and Peter are good now
Oh, so hey, what happened to your golf game yesterday? I was watching it was like fun
But it just kept I don't know it was bad service because it was storming so and then eventually my phone died and then I just fucking I gave up
People were kind of a sagging
Buddy, I don't have all day. Hey dog
What can you got a lot to say when it comes to a fucking woman, but when a man fucking joins you can't say shit
He's a fucking coward this guy's like I shouldn't even wait
First of all first of all you got
Junkie James listen junkie
You're staying with your only girlfriend. You can't y'all believe y'all friend. Don't you game? You're five foot tall
You are an ice cream
Joke
You're a five foot white guy trying to ask anybody to see me
You're a loon. I'm 60 tall, baby. Okay. People have seen
Until you're the same, until you're the same height as me.
You're the same height as me, you're six foot tall.
Same height as me.
Yeah, about the same height as me, I'm five feet tall.
You don't know shit, you just gonna make shit up, faggot.
I am not buddy with sirex you
You are Tony's best friend for ever.
You have no clue what you're talking about.
You have any clue.
You just met me.
You have no clue about me, Tony.
You have no clue about Tony.
You have no clue about anything.
You're Junkie James.
You come on panels to pick attention for people.
You seek attention from people,
and you OD on panels for attention for people.
Yeah, you're a loser, guilty game, you're a joke.
I laugh at you, you laugh at me, we laugh at you Tommy James, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you Tommy James, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you, we laugh at you
You are a joke. You're a joke.
We're talking about people that live online and stay true to your house.
We laugh at you.
I don't care if people hate me.
I'm not here for people to like me.
You think I'm here for people to like me?
You really got me fucked up.
You see that?
He goes right to feed.
Crazy fuck.
The candle where I was hanging out.
Junkie Jane, up here, trying to fuck the cow, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
We know
I'm gonna ramble
You're worthless. That's all you are. You're a low tower. You're a low tower.
You won't even have a combo.
Who got that? You O.D.
Why do you O.D.?
I keep correcting you.
You O.D.
Yeah, I'm O.D. right now.
I'm so O.D. right now.
Turn on the camera, buddy.
Jimmy's buddy.
That's right. He has friends like Jimmy and Tony.
Like, Jimmy and Tony, the biggest heroes in your body.
Those are your kind of bodies.
Everybody's need to do the J.J. Law.
Everybody needs you.
Everybody needs to take doctors.
You're pathetic.
You can't even fucking post a fucking channel.
You're just a fucking chatter.
And you got a lot to fucking say.
You're pathetic.
You're just a junkie again.
Yeah, I've done drugs in my life.
Dude, Eminem?
Eminem called, bro.
They're the red-
So what, how do I make you so I have a rapper, bro?
So hold on, now you're going to try to use the fact that I have talent to get to me.
We have enough wiggers.
I'm playing instruments and I rap.
What's up, bud?
When Jimmy could rap way better than you,
Jimmy could out-wrap your ass, and you'd do that stuff.
Yeah, you can't rap for shit, kid.
You
What happens in her fucking life, why is it your business? Why bother you?
He doesn't want to go where he's at. He doesn't want to show his pet.
I'm just asking, right? If you're going to say it, just why.
Show your pet. Show your teeth. Show your pet.
Show your teeth. Show your face.
You can't afford Wi-Fi? Are you using free Wi-Fi?
Is that how broke you are? Are you using free Wi-Fi at a store?
Like, you can't pay your bill or something, bro? Your phone bill?
He's online right now.
Oh, is that your O-Face?
Is that your O-Face?
Or right there when you get slammed in the ass, huh?
That's your O-Face.
Damn, bro.
You didn't have to tell everybody the O-Face.
I just didn't know you were this much of a coward, to be honest with you.
I didn't know you were this much of a coward.
Coward, by the way.
Yeah, okay.
Tells me to come on panel you don't even turn this fucking camera on what a fucking why do I have to turn my channel
Yes, what's your shitty little bed where you sleep? Let's see
Why are you just sleeping in bed watching psyche?
Um, so she's right here with me
I can understand if some of us are single, but you're a whole-ass married man.
You're laying next to your fucking wife and you're arguing with a panel?
Yeah.
Yeah, why not?
I'm bored.
I'm probably married.
I'm getting called out.
Maybe it's an imaginary wife.
Maybe it's like a...
Like, it's just an imaginary wife.
Imaginary, by the way.
Imaginary now.
I mean, she's pretty quiet, you know?
Why doesn't she fucking say something?
Why?
Because she don't want to talk to morons like you.
Really? But she talked to you all day long, lying next to you and listening to this whole shit.
And, and, Bita, you don't have anybody.
You've got no man, Bita. I feel bad for you. No man wants you, Bita.
i feel really bad for you maybe you gotta change your attitude change your attitude change your
attitude and be humble you gotta be humble beta that's being humble let's be humble
be humble yeah i would be nice i would be nice beta i would be nice you know you know what being
nice is and giving a compliment is it has nothing to do with being a stiffy dumb bitch
it has nothing to do about being a stiffy dumb bitch
i'm being nice i'm being nice you dumbass so in front of your wife you're calling another woman
a bitch what a fucking lovely wife you got bravo my wife my wife's a bitch too what are you talking
about she goes who is that girl she goes who the fuck is that lady with that annoying ass voice
color change avoid easy you're very easy to fuck with it's okay you can't fuck with me
no you can't fuck with me you can't fuck with me wash your face and just come back when you can
wash my face no i'm not you betta i don't just wash my face i can't go full shower okay thank you
That's what you do. You just wash your face. You just wash your face. You don't take a shower. You don't shower. You don't take. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don't wear makeup. You don
I don't have to fucking worry about it.
Yeah, you don't have a man.
You sleep alone at night all the time, Betta.
Beautiful to lay this fuck off all the time.
And how do you know she doesn't shower?
That's fucking weird.
Are you watching her?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
For 14 hours, for 14 hours.
She was on live stream for 14 hours and get her shower.
Get her shower for 14 hours.
First you sit there and tell me to bathe my cats.
Did you know cats don't fucking bathe, idiot?
And now you're telling me to take a shower?
I'm asked, they have groomers, pet groomers.
Ever heard of a pet groomer, you idiot?
Your cats were filthy.
Your cats were have tangled hair.
I felt bad for those titties.
They had tangled hair
and they had a fucking dandruff all over them.
I felt so bad for them.
I was like, she does not clean those cats.
I think you had them right there when you're food and you're talking about your cat when they do their veterinary fucking
Visas on fucking point. They're going to the back and going to the groomer two different things two different things
Going to the groomer and the vet is two different things
I showed you last night if my care is like my cats are black and white
It's not fucking down. You stupid ignorant fuck you want to see I told you. Yeah, so it again cats right now
You're not gonna see anything. No, never mind. Never mind. You probably took them a bath
never mind. They're probably clean now. They're clean now. They're clean now. They're clean now.
I put them in the bathtub and I was like, hey, kiddies, take a bath. Cats are fucking scared of
water. Most of them are. I know. Well, yeah, but you still have to bathe them once in a while.
Oh my god. Why am I arguing with fucking stupid again?
I don't know. You like arguing with stupid. Did you know that cats are natural groomers? They
have Brussels on their tongue. They use 75% of their date as grooming and 25% is fucking sleeping.
Okay, you can really fuck a cat up by taking it to get groomed all the time
You don't take like a cat a fucking six-year-old cat put in the back and then brush like
you do it. I'm sitting taking to the groomer to have some professional take
care of it. Not you. I've had a lot of cats. I've had cats my entire life. I was
raised with cats. Did you take them to the groomer every month?
Yeah, I did. I loved him. I checked I took care of him till the day they
How many times have you taken Raven to the groomers? I would take him to the groomer. They would get their nails turned
You're he's dumb he thinks these are like fucking main cool luxury fucking like they're like these are fucking domesticated small cats
Yeah, they weigh maximum like
12 pounds you can brush them you can like clip their nails if you want if they're like you know
scratchers but they're animals they're animals they're they're actual living things they're not a
toy you have to take care of them you got to feed them you got to bathe them you got to bathe
Well, you can do it easy Google search j-dolls if you're like if you want to know you can do it easy Google search just put it
Do you generally take
Why do they have pet groomers for us
Fucking dogs mostly and there's there are like cats that have long hair and some stupid people like to make them
I like my cats and actually the way they are they're beautiful
Hey, Tommy I'm talking about stupid talking to stupid again
so
So what I've understood I noticed J-Dog always has to stream outside be done
He always has to stream outside because it's his partner that hates this online shit
She makes them stream outside
Partner by the way. No, that's that's that's that prove us wrong. It's easy to prove wrong
See you need to prove wrong, right?
Just tell her say hi
Got a lot to hide buddy
I have none
Sure you don't you're retarded your hedgehog probably has a
Don't have I don't have
What did you say beta
A hedgehog a hedgehog
why are you
what's wrong with the hedgehog
shut the fuck up i wasn't talking
what's wrong with cat
why does she fucking go around
saying cats are soulless
they eat your brain down
they should die so i can say the same shit
she's like you can't stop
aids i said you're even gonna
this black lip gives them a speech impediment
You're just a junkie gang, that's all you are is a junkie, you just shoot up, that's all you do, that's all you do, and you just shoot up, you're just a junkie, you're just here for everybody's entertainment, just OD and just let us all around again.
All we do is laugh at you.
I love that on your stream.
I love you on New Year's stream.
When you were on Sam and Kennell,
when you were on Sam and Kennell, Tommy James,
I loved that stream.
When you almost OD'd two times,
you were begging for attention.
You were such an attention hoarder, Tommy James.
And you're not even a female.
That's the worst part.
You're not even a female.
You're pathetic, Tommy James.
You're pathetic.
I laugh at you.
You're a joke.
I don't care, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I don't give a damn, I
He when he was in jail, he doesn't want anyone to know that when he was in jail
He set it up. He was a CEO and he used to protect people having sex
Used to let him fuck in there
You literally have a cleft lip that gives you a speech and you're junkie. You're a junkie. That's all you are. You're a junkie. Your brain is fried. Your brain is fried. Your brain is fried. You're a junkie. You're a five foot junkie trying to be a rapper. You're trying to be a rapper. You're trying to be a rapper. You're trying to be like a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a rapper. You're a
You try to rap and you can't rap for shit. My boy ruby Jimmy
He doesn't want but he wants to come at people who have no I don't wrap no, I don't wrap I suck at wrapping
You can't you can't I suck at rapping I suck at rapping I suck at rapping
With this clip log
Blow and log. Why do you look like baby Huey with a go key?
Why do you look like baby Huey with a go key and a skull cap?
You look just like Cyrax. Cyrax wears a skull cap, too.
Cyrax wears a skull cap, too.
He wears a skull cap. He wears a skull key.
He wears a skullie just like you you're junkie James does junkie James
You just met me you ain't know how long I've
Nobody likes you Jadah. I don't give a damn. I'm not here for people like you.
So what am I? But you're saying I'm a loser and I'm a drunk and what are you?
You care people like you because you got an OD on streams.
What's for people that would find people's enjoyment? You OD for people's enjoyment on streams.
So OD on streams is because I like it when you drugs or I want attention. What are you talking about?
Both of it both both you're trying to die on live screen. That is the most pathetic thing
What happened when you when you went in the shower when you went in the shower with that blow dryer
What happened when you went in the shower with that blow dryer on New Year's?
You
I'll tell you what I did, but I did it on Sam's panel on New Year's. It's
Your retard
He just makes shit up because he doesn't have it
You're gonna have to try hard.
Jay Dogg is like arguing with a fucking fifth grader.
It's like ridiculous.
It's fucking the worst.
He is literally the biggest fuckwit I've ever met.
got all you have cleft lip faggot you act like i haven't heard that my entire life
you know what you got all up the streaming side and you're all all that hurts my feelings
oh you know what he's talking about he doesn't want me to talk
that's the first time i've heard that wow
that's about you he told us how he protected people get off the audience
get off the audience come up with something creative come up with something creative
you're a rapper right you're a rapper come up with something more creative
Come up with something more creative in your brain.
Oh, I forgot.
All your brain cells are fried.
They're all fried from that fentanyl, you two.
All fried.
Oh, it's terrible.
So fried.
I know.
Why is it fried?
Why is your brain still fried?
Oh, I don't know.
You look like baby Huey.
Why do you look like baby Huey with a little goat key?
Dude, you literally sound like a fourth grader.
You look like a wheelie.
You look like an Oscar Meyer wheelie.
You're not allowed to stream in your house.
You're a ginger.
You have no lies, you lie about everything, you're a f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king f**king
You know as much about me as I do about you, but I know more about you
You go out there trying to fight people and your five-foot call fight foot told me
Yeah
Did you have a stroke man really?
Scum man. Did you have a stroke?
Smoked that cigarette a little harder.
Make sure it likes up all the way. Make sure that cherry likes it all the way.
Like that cherry up all the way. Yeah, light it up. Light it up. Hell yeah. Hell yeah.
Get that voice a little more raspy.
Yeah, I do. Yes, I do. Yes, I do. Junkie James.
100% I love it. I love it. Junkie games love watching you suck on shit. That's why you did what you did when you were in jail
No, I did it because I got paid I let these motherfuckers fuck each other cuz I got paid for it if they went on
Now you're saying what kind of a person you are you mean
Admitting to that fucking shit
This is funny now. We said now we're getting to the good shit not make you a
Yunkie no
No, you have to try harder. You're gonna cap the try harder on me
Yeah, you let a little cigarette you lit up another cigarette. Why are you in your garage smoking in the house?
Yeah, it looks like you're in the garage I can see that unfinished drywall behind you
Yeah, I like to argue what recards
Oh, Jesus. Come on turn it on. Turn it on. I just saw a little
Hispanic gnome in the garden a gnome in the garden. Yeah, he's fucking he's a coward
Ravens like shut up. Watching people fucking jail. What a fucking fruit
Watching people fuck in jail
Oh
He's outside because he's not a lot
He's mad about you smoking a cigarette in your garage or wherever you are
Yeah, what's up with that? You want me to smoke inside? I'm trying not to do that
What a loser. Do you need bounce? Did he really rage quit?
I think he accidentally turned on his cam and then he was backstage
His wife does not allow you to go out
What's up Tommy does not let allow him to go on panels. He's inside. She hates his shit
Really if you want to get rid of Jay dog just send him a pizza his wife yellows at him
He tucks his penis in his tail between his legs and he gets off panel. He knew I was in the back
Right on we're gonna have door knocks, buddy. How does your girl like getting those door knocks?
Mary Mary doesn't like the door knocks matter of fact Mary doesn't like him
being involved in these communities at all and
Tommy might not know your history J dog, but I certainly do I certainly do I he loves sucking the dick
Well, yeah, I don't know what it was yesterday. He was threatening me in the chat yesterday
He's obsessed with you. He's obsessed with you. He would prefer
Beautiful and hit on you. But since you've made it obvious that you don't like him
He he takes the opposite approach and he talks bad to you. But if you come on stream, he's there
He's the first one in chat
He'll try to get up on panel. He just wants to be close to you. Why?
He was throwing you under the bus, he was like, yeah, he's done milk to your house
But okay, that's I just
Well, so what's using our tactics, that's for sure
Yeah, J-Dog targets women time is right. He's been times been watching his stuff forever. He knows J-Dog
He's seen how he moves and that's what he does. He gets obsessed with women and then he stalks them
Kind of you know kind of like what KZ does to be honest
They're both in my eyes KZ and J-Dog are one of the same
They may as well be the same person, but they don't like each other which I find interesting too
Very strange fucking people
Jesus Christ. Yeah, you are. It's actually an epidemic.
I've kind of said that Justine Lady left. I mean, now that she left it, the games can't party.
You know, blacks can't vote because Justine left the chat.
I know.
that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the
Justine was great in Q's chat. She'd always like sent for Q and tell him how wet she's getting and it was funny
No, you absolutely don't stalk women online you do it constantly you've been doing it as part of the reason why no one likes
That's what yeah, that's exactly what he does if I come up here and make fun of KZ and go
Oh, you knucklehead nookie nookie nookie. He'll be like, oh, oh, I'm boxing. What are your friends?
And it's the wrong fucking the wrong docs on top of it. He's a fucking weirdo
Yes, sir. He was on Jimmy's talking about how this dude bunny is this guy fed but fed pass on now
He's he's a fucking idiot
She has everything figured out, but he's one of the dumbest motherfuckers on YouTube
And he hates JD, but the fact is, I mean not JD, he hates fucking J-Dog, but the fact is him and J-Dog are so fucking similar, but I think J-Dog can talk a little better, even with the fucking clubflip.
So, yeah.
I think J-Dog is a...
He talks a lot of shit, you know, in the chat and he goes at almost everybody KZ
He just I don't know if he really goes at anybody
But I mean his history of what he admitted to I don't like at all spitting on some fucking like, you know
your cousin all that fucking shit, but
J-dog will just do all the fuck shit in his life and he'll just judge everybody else
I don't think he's like that judgmental
Well, the people like to take a picture of themselves.
I'm sorry, guys.
He's taking a picture.
He's a fucking weird-looking dude.
I see why he does this.
He's taking a picture of himself.
Is that a real photo?
He can't even talk.
Yet he insists on making everyone listening to him.
He looks like kind of like a weird guy.
Who's better-licking J-Dog or Casey?
I
He's been kicked out all these boards and shit
Yeah, he was having a he was talking to Jimmy about that. Yes, right? Oh, they're in Marty's discord
Like no one's like barely anyone's in Marty's discord. You're just not accepted anywhere
KZ and that's all he wants. He wants to be accepted
He wants people to listen a little fucking mumble on panel and pretend to be his friend
The thing is case not many people, you know, you're not a likable guy is when it comes down to you're just not a likable guy
Just like they tolerate J-Dog really you guys are the same fucking person. I swear it
It's true and the same both both equally unlikeable
Yeah, but they don't they lack self-awareness the solid reason
You know KZ I think has less self-awareness than J-Dog
I think J-Dog kind of knows his place around here, but KZ he's completely
Yeah, though I sound upset KZ or if I just you know telling truths that you don't like to hear
KZ, do I not think give me a truthy smile buddy. Yeah come up and try to talk with your speech abandonment. Oh
It's an accent
He's a weirdo, they're all weirdos
And you know what they both have in common? They both suck groovy Jimmy's dick. That's the only thing they have in common
That's very strange
He kicked me the other day like a bitch cuz he can't have very sensitive boy these
Very sensitive. Yeah, that's something that all these guys are easily triggered sensitive
It's not hard to get them to dance around and just like not even we're talking to them
Just slip a couple jabs in and let them fucking cry, you know
What do you guys think he does one is his wife feeling at him or is he just he wanted to take a shower?
Probably get me all that by his fucking partner guarantee
And we talked to his wife. His wife fucking can't stand up. She can't stand this you two drama
He hates the fact that he goes on panels every time he gets a beat to the roof that much closer to getting it the worst
Yeah, he continues to do it because he's a lonely lonely guy. He's a lonely guy
And then again, I think he has a big crush on you be that's why he's so weird with you
I thought he wasn't married like I thought he's just like who would marry him
I thought it was just an imaginary wife
I've never heard of I've never heard of female none of that
But I know he used the cash up of his wife or ex-wife to donate to groovy Jimmy or something
No
Died
Which was a lie, very much a lie.
You know how it's true, you're gonna try it in the chat.
You want my attention, war dog?
Join the fucking panel, dude. The thing is, what? Are you not eating good?
Do you not have a full plate?
I eat good. I'm feeling good because I gained a little bit of weight because I'm not on a bunch of drugs.
That ain't with me, buddy. You look more healthy, Tommy. You look more healthy.
Also, more dogs from those guys that thinks he's the next YouTube superstar, right?
Living in filth. I know he's a hoarder. He's surrounded by filth.
Yeah. He's another one. He is. And then his dad, you missed me. His dad called him a little
private bitch in his room. They put his like, it's pathetic, his little setup. He literally
lives with mommy and daddy, literally.
So I don't I just remember seeing that he lived in Filth Beach all around him
The grown man that calls himself war dog, which is you know, a very telling
J-dog war dog J. There you go war dog parallel
There you go, it's easy to see it's quite
Remember what people thought me and time were the same person
Those legs don't ever bite. That was funny.
That's a weird one.
I know.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so too.
Fucking funny.
Okay.
Oh.
Okay, that one.
Yeah.
I want to see this toy.
He has toys.
Well, yeah, his whole blue J dogs places not too great either. He did a house
And that's how we got Docs because we got him to do a tour around his neighborhood show this is garbage bins
Yeah, he's a dummy
He came back said that's an Airbnb. No, it's not
When I literally go live from the edge of my bed, do you not watch?
I have a bed. Do you want to see it? It's a big bed. It's quite large.
I have roommates, buddy. I'm not couch surfing.
You do with more healthy Tommy. It's good to see I know I'm healthy. I'm good
Hey, I can pass background checks now after the whole longer thing just went away because the
Stipulation was done for people for a year. I'm going to sign some new hire paperwork today for a good ass job
I can work at hospitals with him and
Ironman homes again and all that shit. So I'm more bitch
But all we want is like, I've been down bad.
Hey, buddy, thank you for coming, Cassie.
Yeah, of course.
Hey, dog, you're socking.
Leave me alone, you weird creepy soccer guy.
Hi, black grouchy.
You're a creepy soccer guy.
Oh, Paige.
I'm gonna make you a shootout.
You think I could have taco salad for breakfast?
What are you making?
Taco salad for breakfast. I'm craving why not whatever you whatever you craving babe
I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I'm not over 40. I
You say you don't like me, but the concept is adding to my attention, but you don't want to talk to me. I don't understand you.
But once again, you told Chad I know that Tommy is not using anything because when he's using he's not in the mood to argue
Called us all about him and his wife's finances and his marriage and I was hit on a lot of the listen to rap music
Good good guy, dude, some of the great guys
You own a house congratulations on owning your house
I can't dude I can't I can't
Yeah, I've been people that can't look when they're talking shit you will ever do that so let's move along
Sorry, what are they saying?
They'll be fighting with each other.
Five properties, yeah.
This sounds like fucking game at the front.
I have two pieces.
This is...
23.
Catch up, by the way.
The thing is, is I'm really not trying to
fucking compare myself with you guys.
Do you still smoke weed on me?
Oh, yeah, of course. I always smoke weed. That's why I don't go around saying I'm sober, I'm sober, I'm clean, like people can tell, people can fucking tell.
Come on, Tommy, I've watched you for the longest freaking time, you know?
I'd be cross-eyed on you, I'd be slugging and cross-eyed.
You were not even in the mood, you were just like, well, you'd just be chillin' and it's like people are backstage and there's like, Tommy, you're like, oh yeah.
Hey, your your camera would be all spinning around.
We had some fun.
All different person.
I don't regret anything.
I don't regret anything in my life.
I'm glad that you and Blogger, like you and Blogger,
were able to, you know, put all that shit aside.
Now, we're similar.
Now, like, we're mainly civil, like, exchange all this stuff.
Yeah.
Like I said, I can pass the background check to my mom.
Alright, for a while I couldn't.
Alright, thank you.
Could you imagine if we made fucking Christmas karaoke albums of Anna?
Kara, could you guys, what would we call it?
Christmas karaoke?
We'll call it Christmas chaos carols.
During Christmas time?
Christmas pearls of chaos and fucking fuckery.
Awards, you know, the most drunk the most, you know, like the loudest, you know, and then we'll have like categories.
Yeah, let's do it right now. Write them all down. Everybody. Let's let's do it. It's a lot of work right now. It's a lot of work. Yeah, I just love that symptom. You definitely are in the category. You're, you'll definitely win that one.
I feel like I'm pretty needed too though, so.
It's going to be a close between J-Dog and Alexander McQueen.
Well, I hope you guys have a lovely
It's all done now J dogs gone we're dogs done. It's all been handled
We're all good
I'll be around later. Thank you guys
My cat says bye as well.
So Paige, are you off today? I am off today.
Good, good. You can relax. I mean, I mean, I know you still have a lot of stuff to do, but
that's a good thing.
Well, I'm kind of glad it's raining out. You know, when it's raining, I don't feel bad for just kind of staying in the house and doing little odds and ends and relaxing a bit. Whereas if it's nice, I don't want to go out to all this golfing.
Rain gives you an excuse to be lazy and do nothing.
Yes, exactly. Perfectly said. Perfectly said.
What is like I feel like psyche is like doing some kind of handiwork assembling something. What is he doing over there?
I'm building an Ikea
Oh, I just I just think just throwing some stuff away. I have a bunch of junk up here. Hold on. I
Just kidding. I'll just take it out
My neighbors gave me a bottle of tequila and I'm a of a Jameson
Okay
watching you like what the fuck is going on he's doing laundry he just went
downstairs to play
noticing that site he's been multitasking a lot on the panel he's like you know
what if I'm gonna be up here you know do my graphic did you fall
No, I just heard the step that you got.
I'm sorry.
He fell down your stairs.
He was secured by the pillow and the blankets.
Yeah.
He landed right on the pillow.
He ran into the wall but didn't spill over.
Oh my God.
What was that?
Are those the speedos? What are you putting on?
I don't know. That's a good thing. It looked like you were putting on like the
American Speedos or something
Nothing too interesting
Sounds like he's having like
Cleaning
This is how I this is how I get off. I clean
My house is up in this clean and like a year. It's big so cool. I'm so excited. It looks so good
Being the cat
Yeah, hey, what's up tricks?
You guys are also excited kitty-kitties, are you doing?
Raven's beans is talking your cats are talking
Keep cats are talking people are talking. I don't know how it goes
My new song
Oh
That's me. Oh, yeah, no, it's really really loud yesterday. She was like being very talkative
I
Think she's doing good. Okay
Got all my cards organized too. So this is really
special
Okay
Yeah
You read my mind page. I was like you want to read the chat do a shout out
Okay, okay, let's shout out to
Let's see. I'll start to the members. I think so shout out to he man shout out to
Uh, Katrina, shout out to Rhea, oh, Rhea Nancy, shout out anyway.
Okay, let me see.
Um, okay, that's all I see.
Okay, everybody else.
Hey, this monkey, this monkey's better.
That was underwhelming.
See you, man.
See you, yeah.
Have a seat.
Good morning mermaid, hold a macaque, Lizzie, Black Archie, fishy fingers, we've got Ivana, we've got Brown Panda, Zimpulse, we have Tommy James, what, who else, Vader, Bud, Reality Nancy, Sassy, Spunky in here, KZ's in here, Bud, okay, you know what, Katrina, hello.
And think that is it. Oh, man. Who did I not say? Did I forget anybody? I'm faked. Forgive me. I think you did good. Yes. There you go. You gotta do it fast. You gotta do it fast.
You gotta make a song about it. Like sing in your English with the chat name. I will.
They have to try to remember your songs, but hold up. Look at you. You don't think it's chucky dog exploded
He's talking to Tommy. He's fine. Okay. Oh, I'm sorry. I don't know. I don't know almost
I'm trying to keep up. Well, he said you start me to all of us are just like
Who are we you're you're back firing? I'm back firing beat is really good at backfiring. Oh
Yeah
My life is actually like a lot more people than I used to be but you know what's funny is like the more things change
Don't want to say the same. That's actually a piece of crystal. This is not. This is a piece of
page
Really fresh on fire
We're not fire ashes is burning. Oh, it's so good. It's so good
This is a Chris and Maurice pick. Oh, okay. Let me go. Hey, was that funny?
Like yesterday someone took a picture of like a black dwarf. I was like, so it's okay picture
But I thought it was okay. I really did. I mean, I don't know why it looks like hey, but it didn't
He did or she I don't know who over was
Never mind
Okay, I'm cleansing the area. I am. It's just totally clean
I mean, this is next to godliness, right?
Thank you. They're getting hercules on us moving for sure. I know I mean, you know hercules
I mean, I can't move the furniture yet. It's basically just
I think about trash. Yeah, I think about my books. I
Have a trash ever stuff to throw away still put the alcohol away
Gotta clean my bedroom. That's crazy. It's the last thing I have to do
Hey Alex, that's how blood I'm going. I thought I was Alex of the staff. That is crazy. Wow. That is really scary
Class
Hello, can I take your order, please?
Yeah, tech support. Yes. Take your order.
Yeah, and then and then
Remember you was like you was like her. Yes
Yep
That was the best movie. I'm gonna watch it later
Everyone's addicted to tacos. I'm gonna make a taco shirt. It's gonna be one of my shirts to the taco shirt
right
Hmm gonna be human tacos
Well, yeah, it'll be my like I'm putting into a fish taco taco shirt. He'll be half me have a fish taco
I can't even hear this or taco or them combined without thinking about you. Oh
Yeah, well
I'm putting fish tacos back on the map
There's a very good. Okay, I'll create my account shit when the wrong
Yeah, I'm trying to get home a video game account
Go lose myself in video games
Rose, okay, but I forget all my names now. It's like over a year
Okay, okay, I found it
Maybe I should smoke a little bit more weed
Maybe I'm in a weird mood
I am too I woke up so early and it's like I got to go and like I probably got to go soon
But I'll stay around for like 15 20 minutes and smoke weed because I got so much shit to do today
Yeah, I definitely can't I became a mom
I'll just do it. I
I'll be back, you know for the third that what does it call?
third Thursday
Yeah for the third I Thursday
It's a great name, by the way.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Yes, I'm going to say, yesterday was Wednesday.
It was a wild car Wednesday.
Wednesday or something.
Third night, Thursday.
I think we have.
It's taco Friday. I don't remember exactly. I'll remember since I'll also remember that one Friday
There's like two like that. It's like you open your third eye or then the other third eye
I don't want to be like, you know, you know, that's your fourth. I think now I'm just kidding
I'm not sure.
Which one is the fourth one?
Oh yeah.
They're interchangeable.
I'm not sure.
Fourth eye?
Oh my.
Oh my fourth eye.
Get down really.
You shouldn't be up there.
Get out off the bridge.
How did you get up there?
if you look at her she's not very like you know cats are really good at climbing
stuff and like they usually land on their feet and like they can jump from
small distances mm-hmm she is not coordinated I don't know what her deal
is she can't she's I'm not trying to laugh at her about like she's some shit
before that I've never seen a cat fail at
She's just cute
I'm not very coordinated
No, I'm not
Aww
Very cute
So good. Look at this. Oh my gosh you guys. She's such a little love bug
Raven's gonna steal the show for like one second. Are you gonna steal the show for a minute?
Okay
Look at how she's doing. Come here, baby. Did I say hi?
She's sitting with her paws like this.
She does the R.
Come here.
You need to do it again?
No, because it's not as cool if I do it for you.
She's just sitting there watching.
You're so nice, baby.
She's like, teach me how to be a cat.
You're not a cat. You're a little...
You're not a cat.
You're like a bat and a kangaroo and a cat.
And rabbits.
Oh, how cute.
She's so cute.
It sounds like somebody's house. Oh, yeah, that's not like Marcy's family. She's married to rabbit or is it she?
I forgot, I don't know.
He's my favorite when Marcy's always like, every time, just a couple times randomly in a panel or like shot,
she'll be like, so I got some kittens if you want, anybody want kittens?
Yep, I have too many, so.
It's pretty close.
No more, no more.
No, I wouldn't love another cat though.
I would if I could, if I was...
Ready to go to the nut house already. I'd get more cats
I'm ready. Yeah
No, no, no, I'm not you I mean
Like he I have questions for you about psychedelics next time you open panel
Yeah, that goes face first part two or the second
Or 11
Or just not like why per focus on the last two
Yeah
Because as we go space killer
Second
Yep, you have eight cats
The boss a lot. I've had it. I've had as many as 11 or 12. I had the kids
No, they said they hate cats. They're snobby little pricks. Oh
Yeah, see I'm reading everything wrong. Shit. Thank you. Thanks for freaking out being like I feel like because I have these tiny glasses inside me
I just read like, you know, yeah, you guys like do the shortcut. Okay. Hey, ancient case. I was like, I saw you meant eight cats. They're all snobby little pricks. That's what I was going to say. His cats are all brats.
Brat cat.
Brat cat. Brat cat. This is you are maybe a little bit bratty.
Let me answer you.
Let me just stop singing today, Paige.
Paige should be a musical.
Paige, you'd be great as a band.
What's it called? They're called the band trumps or the band tramps?
What is it? The sound of music?
The band trumps, the band trumps, right?
You would be a great musical, so would Bida.
What?
A great what?
In a musical as well.
Oh yeah, but which one? Which one? I would be good in probably, I don't know, Phantom of the Opera?
I'm not gonna lie, I'm not a big fan of musicals, so I don't watch them, but I mean...
You don't like musical?
No, I can't see like I'm psyche wearing like, you know leggings or they do
Have to wear they're like ballerinas or something. Yeah, well, yeah, you do you wear dancing shoes and do like freaking, uh, you know
Peter Pan or Prince Charming
Mm-hmm. Yeah, who is it? You would you not be here Peter Pan is played by a woman on stage always. Oh, he's so upset
Not Peter Pan
I could probably be like Captain Hook Peter Pan is played by Kathy Rigby and like all these like you know females
It's very famous female character. We'll give you a pair of forest green Lulu's
No, thank you. I'll be too tall for Peter Pan. Peter Pan is like six foot three. He's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he
Yeah
Don't make fun of Leo's
My gosh
Yeah, Leo charts he man
Leo
For Philip, Prince Philip is Sleeping Beauty all Prince Philip. Isn't Prince Philip the one that like the city was like Jeffrey F. Seed's friend or something?
We can remake so on. We can remake Cats. We're all be cats.
But it's just a weird, it's just a really bad movie though. Isn't it weird?
Like the worst outfits ever, Casley.
Um, or pretty disturbing that I don't know. Yeah, they do look kind of creepy
In the real movie them in the movie, too, they were fucking pretty though. Oh my gosh, they're like
Mike it's like almost like remember that Mike Myers when he was the cat in the hat. It's like that creepy. I was like that
Right in the quad
That was a weird
Mr. Humberflue, he's just a prick firing at everybody.
Mr. Humberflue, I don't even remember that one.
That was just one of Grace's favorite movies when she was little. I had to watch it 80 billion times a day.
You know, when they go through those phases, they have a favorite movie and then yeah, you have to watch it for a long time, a lot, every day.
Oh, yeah, then David, you know, they do like to watch some movies over and over and over, right?
Oh, happy birthday to your son.
Whose birthday is it?
Katrina's son.
Oh, happy birthday Katrina's son.
Oh, it's our man, Paige, I've always been a friend of him.
Oh, yeah, we're fine.
How old is your son?
It's like a teenager party.
There's a difference in those parties for sure.
Good idea, Thym.
Paige needs to make some pictures of everyone,
make cat pictures of everyone with AI.
Then for you, Thym,
he'll put one of those cats,
just like the one you have on your dog.
Yeah, I'll just start doing AI drawings and stuff. I'll put the right, but it's gonna be hard.
Those are harder to deal with unless you put someone's picture through the...
No, I was cursing at Paige. I was cursing at somebody in the chat and you have no idea what was going on.
And that person you were like talking to and they like definitely talked to me about it the next day.
Not Paige, but I was talking to somebody else in the chat and Paige thought I was talking to her
Oh my god, look at this is like a two hundred twenty seven dollar
Look at this a two hundred twenty seven dollar key to the other box
It's a two hundred twenty seven dollars and forty six percent off and it's two hundred twenty seven dollar forty three percent up
$227
It has an app an app runs the
Yeah, those are cool except like one of my cats a little afraid of one. So I gave mine to my friend
It's like
But they use they save you in the long run, you know with the litter and also like the hassle
Like three hundred four hundred dollars
This one doesn't even look that nice. It's made of plastic. I mean, it's not like it's not like it's like
Night, it's like I don't know not like that fancy. I don't know why it's expensive ridiculous
$300
Yeah, but you say
I try to teach my cats to use the toilet it actually did teach one of my cats how to use the toilet
That's one of them ran away unfortunately, but he didn't use the toilet
Yeah, they have um toilet kits where you can keep like kids how to or cast how to use the toilet
You know just like that for kids. They put like a smaller one a
Little mini one on top of the toilet to train them. It's like this little thing
Yeah
This one this one's like a real toilet
It's got privacy and everything. Yeah, it's got like full seat and shit. Oh my god
Yeah, this cat's a cat's gonna have a nicer bathroom than I have this year. Oh
It's okay. You know the cats like to go outside. They don't even use the litter box. It would be just a waste
Let's see self-cleaning though there really doesn't clean itself you do have to like empty it out, you know
Okay, uh, we are getting glass are starting to your root of smart psychies here to say yeah
I'm thinking about getting another pair. It's not him. He's one. I'm gonna get like a nicer pair
Um, because I really like them in there. I can see and I think they look pretty good on me and uh
I'm kind of smart. I do but I don't know someone set up somebody. It's funny. It's like one of the dumbest people they ever met. So
You're one of the one
I said I was dumb so was that I think was Alex or something. I thought I was a retard or something
I'm not I'm not going to but he was so big don't mean
Look at my hair today, they braided
Who did this I can fairy I think a fairy in the middle of the night who's the horses tails and look at it
Have it in my man. It's like all something something about Mary style
It's not it's not it's not it's not covered in cum beta. It's like it's not it's up like a break. I think I'm brave
It's sticking out
You're getting
It's a completely
Completely
No, they came in
Hold out a piece of your hair, and then they drew they braided that piece and they left. It was a fairy the fairies
Fucking fairies
Well, I love that I love them, but I I mean I like hate some of them
Some of them it's pretty weird because you do have straight hair. Yeah
It is weird. I've never I mean, I don't remember ever having to happen and it's like feels so perfect that it's like
Weird it's like and then remember I woke up with that burn to like a few weeks ago
That was weird too. That was weird too. And I still have that let me see
Yeah, it's still there. Oh
I mean, it's not not very strong there anymore. It's pretty much faded away. It's still there a little bit
Yeah, it's pretty much healed
Something else happened to someone like that was similar to that that was also part of this community up on panel at the same round the same time
Paranormal activity someone someone had like the worst
So someone had like it's like
Remember I remember just remember and like I don't have an exorcist and I'm around because he would carve his
He would carve his name on their chest or something like ready. They're asleep and then be like oh my god
That's that Freddy fucking did this to me. I was like, I seriously woke up and it's like Freddy
Did you care? I got it. I just feel like the boiler room boiler room burn
They probably say your eyes shut or something. Oh my god, okay, not be so
No, maybe when you're sleeping one of the cast braided your hair
It's a thing at the reddit thing
Okay, yes, it's hard page is hardcore. Hey
Okay
Yeah, I'm looking at some of those cats
You've had a good sale on print hair braiding cats
Don't think they can look a lot of them in industry
Cats doing weaves
Check braiding
But you just make them do it on AI. It's too hard to trade them to do that in real life
But do it to have them do it on AI. They'll do it. I've seen a cat go to the gym and stuff
Really cool. Yeah
And he made it because there's another cat. There's another cat cat with it
I think it was a cat or dog these dogs or the dogs were like making fun of me just skinny
And he starts working out and then like
And then at the end of the video they'd see he runs with him again
And they ran away because he's like so big now. He's got all big above
Yeah, there's a video with like a whole bunch of cats that AI cats that are
They're doing dives into the pool
they're like professional Olympic divers you know how they like get on the you
know that's hilarious I dive in boards or whatever mm-hmm I don't know I forgot
who sounded to me just imagine a cat walking to the gym like on his like two
legs and somebody be like damn you hi no bro I'm AI I don't know why that was
funny in my head but not allowed
I'm going to go talk to Salad though I think and maybe I will have a nice day.
My ass won't be back.
You have a nice day too.
Bye bye.
Okay, so you know what actually the cool glasses there was these ones will click magnetic reading glasses for men are
And so they click right here, but there's a smooth
There's a movie called the jerk I think is Steve Martin and he actually imbents the same kind of thing in that movie and give them
like a millionaire
but then
Magnus wait magnitude. I want to go cross-eyed remember that one
Called the jerk. I think it's called the jerk right early. What is it Steve Martin right guys the jerk?
Is it like the two guys that are like con artists and they're trying to like con this other lady that has money?
I think it was Roxanne, maybe that was Roxanne, but the jerk was about he he was like adopted by the
Black family and he's like Steve Martin's like the whitest person in the world and he actually thought they were
You know what the movies back then they were funny, but now if you think about it, they're pretty freaking racist, you know
Yeah, yeah called on soul man. I don't know if you remember that movie
And it was about some white guy that I wanted to get into like Harvard, but he couldn't get in like and then
You know because they have like applications for people that are like, you know minorities
He went and like, you know, like change the color of his skin got his hair all curly
It's called stoma and then he gets in
And he has to like pretend like he's black through that, you know, whole college thing.
Yeah.
This is black girl, and like he falls in love with her, and then he finds out that he actually took her sludge.
She was like the next one to, you know, get into the college.
I don't know if anybody's ever seen that, but it's supposed to be like a love story, but if you watch it now, it is pretty fucking racist.
So he's wearing black face. He's basically in black face, you know
It doesn't but it does the way in brothers of the white chicks
I did a white face and then like, you know, it's like those are kind of controversial, you know
But kind of not anymore black faces kind of
I don't think you would be a word. I don't think they'll be me. They'll be making that kind of movie these days now
Yeah, I would be
She sees the man and it's about this like it's like kind of like
And it's like this girl goes to high school, but she's like it has to be a guy and she like just like a guy
But then it's like a seed where she goes like in the locker room
And she's like, there's like a whole like naked shower scene, it's like the weirdest movie and then she's like trying not to make it in the shower, it'll be with figures.
Wait, what was the name of the movie?
It's called She's the Man.
And it's not the one with, it's not the one with the, what's the guy, Ashleigh Taylor.
What's the guy's name?
The real weird girl that went kind of crazy.
She's real popular throughout her name though.
There's one before that, it was like from the 90s, we have to look for the 90s one.
Who was that chick though?
Remember that chick that was like really popular and then she like then all of a sudden she her like lips
We got all big and she like
Had like her hair all crazy and was wearing wigs to court and stuff. You didn't remember it was just famous
She's she's okay. I don't know. No one's don't say I wish I wish
Chats sometimes is on top of it, but come on guys. You would know
Ashley they've asked me since it's Ashley's up there. I remember
Amanda Hein there we go. It's Amanda Hein
Okay, okay. Yeah, I remember her. No, no, Amanda. My name is Amanda Bynes. Yeah, I'm fine. Yeah. Yeah
Mm-hmm. Yeah
So, yes, she went kind of cuckoo, um, and uh, you know, I don't actually do it now, but
It's hard you ever see how about you ever watch that's a Raven because I got him and that show we named Orlando Brown
He actually got like one of the worst tattoos I've ever seen in my life of Raven Simone on his neck
And then he always goes around to interviews saying that he slept with her or she's like no
He's actually got insane like he he has a weird like yellow lenses. He saw her yesterday. That's why he knew she was insane
Oh, she's still I mean she looked pretty crazy last time I saw her on the TV, but I haven't seen her for years
I don't think
But uh, yeah
You know is
Disney stuff like our like Mickey Mouse Club or in when you're
That age is not a good age to become famous because that's gonna be like probably the top of your career, right?
It's not usually gonna get any better and so it and you don't want it your life to get worse, but
But uh, yeah, it's hard. It's hard to because like a lot of times it's when they are when they are
Sorry when they are around that age the parents will take all their money and stuff like that
Yeah, it's like then they're not living like, you know, they're they're youth. You know, they're just almost being I don't know
I think it's yeah, it's yeah
Yeah, I mean even thank you like there are years where they should be like having innocent fun and that kind of stuff
but I mean
Yeah, they really want to do it from like an early age. That's what they want to do. It's their passion
But if your parents are like, oh, yeah, I want to hear it's cute
I want to like, you know make money off of you. That's yeah, I think
Only ways they know only what's only the only ways like now you can make
Sorry
Hey, what's up, baby?
Hi, yes, but they used to have like these work laws where you couldn't work, right?
You couldn't work, like, you know, if you were like, you know, they're called child labor laws, right?
And so when they, the babies on the show, like, you know,
Mary-Kate and Ashley Olson.
They had twins and they, so every, like, they had twins to split up the filming schedule and the, I don't know.
So there's always twins as the babies and stuff. One of the guys
Terry is discriminating against in the summer job.
You guys are one of them, you know.
Is sick you let me see go to let's see what is this plot just one of the guys
Okay, so that's what that's what I'm talking about just one of the guys Terry feels discriminated against when the summer job
Did the Sun tribute and go to two guys just nice to do something about it. Yeah
She's just like she basically looks like a shit. Like it's like like a
From Mary with children or something. She's just like a lesbian. She doesn't really look like a guy
But it's interesting movie. Hey, babe. What's wrong?
She kind of turns into a Bush lesbian, but it's fine.
I think the weirdest movie I've ever seen is like,
it was called something like,
Hedwig and the Angry Inch.
Angry Inch, the Angry Inch.
That's great.
You've just seen that?
Yeah, I love it.
I think it's the movie, but it's like really weird.
I wasn't expecting to see that.
I just walked into, you know, I was like,
you know how you used to just walk into a theater
and watch something?
Me and my ex, me and my ex let it watch it.
I like it.
It's like a little like, what the hell is this?
But yeah, it's stupid.
I watched it again last year and it has really good music.
I love it in music.
They made a, oh, they did it on Broadway.
Neil Patrick Harris played them.
He played the character, yeah.
Very good music. I love those you guys see this. There's a song at the beginning. It's really good. Oh shit. Hey, babe
Please stop. Hey, babe. There we go. Good kitty
Little tricksy little cheeky. Yeah, just one of the guys with the female act
Female acting actors already looks more male. Yeah, she was already kind of a
Yeah, masculine more masculine looking good girl
Yeah, so I don't know. I haven't really watched a movie in a while
Like but I used to look like these have all these movies where they would have like, you know
They would have like these extreme
Changes, you know, they just like just a shallow how remember instead of like hiring a fat actress
He just hired
Wait, they put Glenn Paul turn a fat suit for the movie, you know
It's like like she didn't really need to do that was that necessary to see they haven't had it
I mean, it's so funny. They you don't even see her face most of the time. So it's like, why does he even have to?
Bother but they could even hire a fat actress for that movie. It's crazy
Okay, my movie is pretty fucking funny though
He sees everybody fat, everybody fat, skinny, and vice versa.
Yeah.
It's hilarious.
I feel like, but it was like very exaggerated, like to go to dinner and like she sits down
and all of the characters collapses, everything shatters.
Like she, and then she eats like 100 plates of food and stuff like that.
It's kind of unrealistic.
What's wrong with the chair?
Yeah, he's a care better chair. What is he going on there? So mad
So kind of wonderful is another yeah, I mean the 80s films were something there. They're pretty they're pretty good, you know
90s yeah, no, no, no the movies kind of stuck. I think they're just getting worse and worse. I mean, it's like they were
They were good at one point
Don't know. There's there's some search. They're still good movies, but it's like they're rare, right?
It's like a few they probably three or four year. I can even watch
We see you sleep
You'll sleep in the theater. No shame. Yeah, I try not to I feel like it's a waste of money to fall asleep in the theater
I know oh
I tried it. Oh
gosh
There's certain movies that you wouldn't be like when I was like a lot younger. I watched a movie on bogey nights
You can't fall asleep to that movie. There's some you can't fall asleep too
But yeah, there's other ones that are just taking too long to get somewhere and you're just like, okay
What's happening and I need to wake up and it's like you're in like middle of the movie like what the fuck is what is this about?
Yeah, I can't stand that and it's like or it's like three-hour movie
I cannot watch a three-hour movie like probably not like it all in a row like I cannot
We don't we don't have
Attentions fans longer than two hours. I don't think even beings do it's like I mean now. It's like so hard to
Markey Markey remember the Markey Mark movie it was called
The crush, the crush, yeah, you ever see that one?
That's a good one.
It's like he's like a bad boy,
and he's like, this is like a rich girl's stadium,
and then he like starts to like.
You know right to her dad and then they and all of a sudden it was like a really good. Oh, yeah
I remember he was like a stalker. Yeah. Yeah
He was like a doctor and he was like, yeah
Yeah, exactly
Or what was that other movie poison ivy would drew Barrymore
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, those were definitely unique. Yeah
Letter yes lover that was
Yeah, lover that was a really that movie always really tripped me out
Really take a platter. Have it. There's also lawnmower man lawnmower man, too. Yeah, that's the same
Yeah, Jacob's lighters good lawnmower man
All the Stephen King 80s movies are kind of better than the 90s ones like the 90s ones pretty much stuff
the 80s ones were pretty good and then
You know, I liked all the fantasy movies from the 80s
I like they like the Disney movies from the 90s setting those were like the best some of the best Disney movies
Beauty and the Beast little mermaid and
Lion King, right?
I did it because we saw them in like the El Capitan, which is like the
This is like oh my Disney is on Hollywood Boulevard. It's like this really nice old-fashioned theater
Yeah, we have these premieres at that. We would go to a nice dinner in Beverly Hills and stuff
Nice times
I think I like these ones
I like these glasses a lot, and they're much more soft.
They're called like those.
You can't really tell much from the...
There's also, there's like a Jeffrey Dahmer-style glasses, too.
I mean, they're just called A.B.
I guess they're the A.B. at our readers.
Yeah, they usually don't have yellow on them. They have the blue block on them.
Have you been to the DMV recently for like, you know, when you go get your renewal fare ready?
Did you pass the eye exam?
Yeah, my eyes were fine when you're reading. Yeah, I mean I'm near sighted
I mean it's like I'm now I'm I was near sighted before I had my late thick and now I'm far-sighted
I think because now I can't see I can't see it all near anymore. I used to see really yeah
We love Tim Curry. Tim Curry was also in a clue. He was then it he was in
He's lost up
Tim Curry yeah, oh, yeah, he's in my picture show get the Dahmer ones. Oh, yeah, I'll show you what they look like
Alicia
Is that is yeah, would say something like that
Oh shit, okay
I look up to the aviators aviator
Yeah, they're all good
And like that a little bit. Yeah, I do actually like those. They kind of look like gray vanish
Yeah, it's a bunch 20 bucks. Yep
20 bucks
Good reviews. They're anti blue light glasses blue blockers
High quality frames. Yeah, I mean
These were like 15 bucks. These are like 15 bucks. They're pretty good quality. They feeling this
That's the chat anyone but anybody like fancy readers you like those ones. Oh, yeah, okay
I'm gonna get those ones. I was gonna try to return these ones
But I think I have time to still and I can exchange them
But we need a mixed track of all psyche's noises. No, no, no, no fuck. Yeah. Yeah, I should do some
Well, when I get to the hundred
Members I can add more
emojis and I'll get I'll put a no no no emoji and I can put a
Okay, oh fuck emoji
And I can pour and bomb emoji or something like that. I don't know. It could be some cute. I have cute ideas
I can do them now, but I'd have to delete some of the
Yeah, you might make a remix of him. He's no no no no no no and oh
Fuck and then also
Or when he's gonna go
Yeah
This is your secret movie you watch anytime white. Oh young Paul Rudd. Oh
There you go. Yeah
Paul read using clueless. Yeah, he played her brother in the movie and love interests as well
Yeah
cats scratch noises
Lobby yep, so
Me just
Take care of some stuff and okay, sweetie. Have a nice day. Love you later. Love you, too. Okay. Bye. Bye
Uh, yeah, okay guys, let's see. I guess I'll just read out of a book for a little bit
Let's do seven o'clock three. So yeah
I don't feel like walking all the way to 7-eleven today. So
I'll wait until 9 a.m. The screaming. Yes, he makes when I'm shocked. Yep
I can't I say no no no and that would make fun of it, but it's like I'm trying to say no no no because it's like
That's what goes through my mind. It's like stop. No. No. No
This is like that's how it happens. Like no, don't do that. They don't keep doing it
Okay, so I
Have a shit. I have a really a lot of cool books here
interesting stuff okay well I'll just read a little bit I don't know if anyone wants to read
I mean I'll do readings let me see if 730 I'll start doing that until then and if you know if
no one wants to hang it's okay okay so this guy's name is his name is HDTutor
to
He's a best-selling
Author on YouTube that he raised to really good books and so let me see
So he read the no-contact you write he's write a lot of books to like a lot
I see like 50 books right here. They're kind of short and sweet
But they're good info, okay
Okay, so
I only have like 10,000 books. So it's okay. So we have the devil's toolkit. So I'll be more of the devil's toolkit
So we're reading about these tools. These are the tools they use
So here's the one of the tools they use when they when they Hoover, right?
It's called the Charming Sander.
Let's imagine a belt sander.
OK, so I said, Charming Sander is another tool which sits
in the Hoover section of my toolkit.
It is used to smooth everything over in an instance.
You will be familiar with the fact
that we must create chaos and drama everywhere we go
in order to provoke an emotional reaction.
And as a consequence, we garden fuel.
Fuel, that's like.
That's what they're after basically. That's the whole theory of it. It's like they're after this kind of fuel that they get. This brain, little adrenaline rush they get when they get some kind of attention, right?
So I lost count of the number of times I've heard comments such as these.
He just walked it back in as if nothing had happened.
He creates a scene and then second later is all smiles and pleasantries.
He hurls a grenade into a room and then pops back later and carries on as usual.
Or he breezes in without any care or concern.
So it says that is because we're entitled to do what we want.
This sense of entitlement is not based on nothing, it is built on a foundation of our
natural superiority over others.
We know that we are better than most of the people around us.
This is a simple fact.
This is why we react when the spotlight is not on us.
We cannot understand why someone else should be receiving any attention when they are not
as great as we are.
We are the star of the show.
And it follows that the spotlight should be firmly trained on us, and you should be watching
and open mouthed awe at our magnificence.
Thus, because we are special, we can do as we like.
We think of you that you do not really mind what we do because you feel privileged to be able to spend time with us
Look upon us and have some kind of access to us to give it this way
Let us suppose you have sat down in a sandwich bar
Having selected a delicious looking BLT and a smoothie for lunch
You're placing your mobile away in your pocket or bag when you should walk towards
Who should walk towards you but your favorite film star to sit down and take one of your
sandwiches without asking and here she eats it.
Which you complain, of course you would not.
You are excited to be in the presence of the star and they even ate one of your sandwiches.
What a great...
What a great story that is to tell your friends.
Well, the situation is similar to us.
You are fortunate to be able to spend time
with someone as marvelous as us,
and this means that you should not mind
that we do as we please.
You should be grateful that you are allowed to be with us.
You do not seem to grasp this, however,
when we act in our entitled fashion,
this causes you to react.
We face something about dichotomy when this happens.
On the one hand, we're delighted
because you have provided us with fuel.
On the other hand, we are affronted because you have failed to acknowledge our greatness
and you have caused us to attack us in some way.
In certain instances, our behavior may cause you to threaten to leave us or do something
similar which may interest puncturing or severing our supply of fuel from you.
We cannot allow that to happen as we reach for the charming standard to smooth over the situation.
The charming standard principally, although not exclusively, operates through word power.
Since we're experts at knowing what makes you tick, we also know the right things to
say to cause you to calm down and thus prevent you from carrying out the threatened action
which we wish to avoid.
The sander is good for all occasions when we wish to grind down and wear away even the
most stubborn of resistance.
We know that you would much rather have peace and serenity.
You want everything to be good between us and you want that golden period so much.
The sander is used to promise that everything is really all right and the golden period is available to you.
All you need to do is stay. The sander is not abrasive in the slightest, which is one of the peculiarities in terms of how it manages to smooth away your resistance.
But it does. The gentle and repeated action of telling you how wonderful you are, how we belong together, how nobody means as much to me as you, all work to remove your stubbornness.
The sander comes with different heads, which we apply as we see fit.
There is a compliments head, which works by repeatedly making compliments about you in
order to rub away any feeling of resentment.
There's also the apologetic head, which is very effective at overcoming resistance by
the issuing of apologies and declarations of sorrow and remorse.
The fact that they are not genuine does not have any impact on their efficacy, and the
head works well.
In addition, there is the promises head, which operates by suggesting a whole range of pleasant
and inviting things will happen.
This ranges from promises that our behavior will change through to going on an exotic
cruise together and includes completing that overdue DIY project, cutting down on drinking
and spending more time together.
In difficult situations, it may be necessary to use the standard as an alternate between
these three heads.
This way your resistance to our overtures will be worn away and you will do what we want.
You should note the sander can also be used in the seduction phase of our entanglement.
It is at that juncture, just as the promises and complimentary heads.
which are used because there will not be anything to apologize for.
It is unusual to encounter much resistance at the seduction stage,
since you are invariably much more willing.
But there may be a little bit of caution on your part
when we smooth away, which we will soon smooth away.
For the most part, the charming standard is used when there has been a problem
and you're going to do something that we do not want, such as leave us.
In such an instance, we will whip out the standard and put it to work.
it is a subtle device and you may often not be aware of just what it's doing since the
application is rather pleasant. Notwithstanding this feather light touch, the standard is highly
effective at removing even the most stubborn resistance. So that is the way to, the way is
clear for us to get what we want. There we go. So it's a little bit dark guys. Dennis Davidson's
And
Carlos Johansson
Your favorite Irby. Oh my god. You look like a troll doll. I thought it's a troll doll or that a real person. Wow
That noise
I'm kind of lawnmower outside. Okay, so that was pretty interesting though
Um, is there any more I want to read before I go because that was the end of that one pretty much, okay?
Hi guys, okay
A lot of interesting books though, okay
And I love
New books
Okay, so I can read the board on the rodent day. So oh no think okay here you go that you guys
Give me shout out your sign. I'll read read some books. Maybe about your sign. Okay looking at snooker. I need to
In my link too. There you go
Okay
Okay, here's a streamer like
Ten likes guys can you do me a favor and like the stream please you got 30 people in here
Thank you
Why do you have my name use my name? Are you impersonating me now? I am I promote your channel
I'd be calling into other streams now
And so I always bring up the fact that yo, I'm a go you guys want to see some cool shit
Make sure you guys subscribe to the channel down below and my name, you know, thank you
Appreciate that. That's very nice of you. Yeah, I mean, you know, I'm trying to do what mods don't do
You know, I'm trying to work my way up trying to get that mod membership again, you know
It might happen, right? I do miss having a wrench in the chat. I see people that
Haven't donated. I'm like damn, bro
Well, I mean, I think everyone pretty much has donated that
I think or at least you know, they're time. They're time their energy their love
I'm like they don't they don't even call in bro. Do you even know like what they look like you see me?
You know, I'm like damn, I got no love
We have to prove yourself to me, but you haven't been hit given in the chat
You're still there. Hello
Yeah, hello. Yes
The cat is licking a snow cone. Okay, so there's Lindsay Lohan. It's also funny. You had a little crush on her Katrina. She's so satchel
I didn't say donations Katrina. I said I said
Supportive support it as they have their time time energy that those are all
Okay, I consider I consider and if you're even here, that's the donation of you. I mean, that's like, you know, you're
And if you do if you do a mod and stuff like that you are you know, no one has to be or it's like so
It's like just appreciated. I know I know it's a very
thankless job as a difficult job and yeah, so I ended up they don't equal ranch, but
Yeah real quick
What what are there?
Real quick real quick
Um real quick. So beta beta and a page has as Peter. Sorry this beta apologized the page. I
Don't know what I do that. Do you have a conflict?
Yeah, she was cursing how to do today and I'm like, yo, I've never heard page say anything bad to you
Why are you attacking page like this?
Oh, okay. Well, maybe she's not in a bad day. I don't know. I know I know she was that's what's bad
You know alcohol they'll always say yeah, I was drunk. You know, I don't remember, you know, that's
That's a disgusting
Excuse
Sometimes people don't remember
Yeah, well, maybe you should know your limits, you know, maybe stay away from the liquor
But it's called test. You know, sometimes you test your limits, right? Hey, they were from liquor. Yeah, it's happening too often though
Have you bored too often?
He's lying in the chatter layman on the alcohol. Yeah
Yeah, I was lying, you know, I'm always lying, you know
She doesn't remember shit, you know, she drinks fucking 18 hours
But I'm not you know, I'm lying. It's okay. No, it's okay
I'm not even drinking alcohol right now very much very much alcohol. So I think
I'm weird now
Alcohol is not part of it and he thought it was her
Okay
I mean, it's like saying it's like me saying right now
Psychi go fuck yourself. And then you're like, whoa, what are you like like that?
Dude, no, dude. I wasn't talking to you. We'll talk on your chat
Yeah, but you say way to go fuck yourself. You say go. He said psyche go fuck yourself though. You didn't say that's what I'm saying
She was attacked in peach
I don't know. I don't I don't believe it. I
Just know I can't believe it
That is what it is. And then she was also attacking summer can't and and Christine can't deny those
Leave the best, I'll be right. Oh, okay
Well, I won't miss him.
Yeah, I'm just kidding.
Okay, okay, let's see.
Yeah, let me tighten this, okay?
Okay.
So, okay, so someone said Taurus, right?
So let me see that Taurus.
I can, I'm not gonna read the whole,
this is like, these are long,
so I'll just read a short part of it, let me see.
Well, this is actually called. Oh, so this is all Vita, too. Yeah, Vita is your Taurus too. So let's do the Taurus game. Okay
Let me I'll be a little bit more
Okay, so Taurus it says what's okay Taurus a chapter 3 Taurus April 20th through May 20th
It says what's mine is mine. What's yours is mine?
It says elements earth
Taurus earth is like a swamp filled with ancient trees covered in moss
Maneuvering through the bog feels like a dream in which you try to walk, but you get nowhere
Quality fixed tourist is like the original immovable objects symbol the bull bullish bullheaded raging bull full of bull
Ruler Venus the goddess of lust jealousy and hedonism
Favorite pastime passing judgments over dinner favorite book the gluttonous gourmet role model uncle Scrooge
Dream job hanging judge a hanging judge key phrase. What why do you make me hit you in the body part?
This road is usually sore from bellowing
As an approach with caution, Taurus, the second sign of the zodiac, resides at the house of
money and possessions.
Traditionally, astrology kindly describes the fixed earth sign as a steadfast, discriminating,
thrifty homebody who is a great cook.
Your real-life version more closely resembles a stubborn, judgmental, boring miser with
a weight problem.
Well, this is kind of a mean book.
I'm sorry.
As mentioned, Taurus and most people conjure up a mental image of Sagittarius, Monroe Leafs,
He's fully chewing sweet grass and batting his big bovine eyes
and pleasant contentment.
Lean across the fence and he'll let you scratch behind his ears.
Climb over that fence and attempt to pick a few of the daisies
growing in the pasture.
You know, soon discover the dark side of tranquility,
raging bull.
With practice, you can spot an immediate, imminent change.
His or her face darkens visibly as the temper rises.
The eyes veil, the jaw jets or sets ever so slightly.
Someone consciously lower a head to a bit.
as you as a real bull does before it charges.
Depending on how self-control it is,
you'll have one second to a few minutes to brace yourself.
There's Venus rules, tourists, and here,
this ancient bad girl bestows an insatiable appetite.
Bulls can never get enough approval, possessions,
food, sex, or rest.
Bulls are emotional not intellectual relying on instinct rather than fact
They often fall victim to their own judgmental natures being born without the seeing another person's point of view
Gene has voided all reason and logic arguing your case will only enrage them and trace you
Prove your point and tourists will simply blink those big soulful eyes and look at you as if you're speaking a foreign language
And it says if you love one a tourist woman will read the tourist woman
Okay, so it says if you love on a tourist woman it says the trouble with some women is that they get all excited about nothing then marry him ah
Okay, share May 20th. Okay, so she has she has mother earth in a black teddy
She's faithful
Courageous and strong the tourist woman seek security and a dependable mate money is not important as long as you can provide a nice home
And the basic necessities she has a refreshingly simple viewpoint of life
Picture fresh baked bread, a cozy loveless, her dainty hand in yours, before you fall in your knees to offer that engagement ring.
Picture an iron hand in that little velvet glove.
She's also tough as nails no matter how hard she tries to convince you and herself otherwise. She's also a victim
You on the other hand we've a bastard from the instant you slip the wedding ring on our finger
Don't forget it if you argue beware
She has all the wrath of her male counterpart in the same pension for violence without hesitation
She will throw whatever she happens to have in her hand including a butcher knife at your head
Food is an emotional pleasure. She will eat when she's happy, depressed, angry, or just plain hungry, which is most of the time.
By her second anniversary, her summer wardrobe will consist of an oversized blue mu-mu and flip flops.
In winter, the mu-mu will be red and she'll replace the standals with hunting socks.
She'll pull the whole outfit together with a wooden shawl. A woolen shawl she found at the secondhand store.
Along with the weight gain will come a natural slowing down of the urge to keep the house
tidy.
Her reasoning will be that it only gets dirty again.
She will however expect you to work two jobs to pay for her new car.
She deserves that for putting up with you.
She likes to start family feuds, then sit back and observe the mayhem.
Emotionally as sensitive as a drill sergeant, she spouts orders, makes pronouncements, plans
everyone's future, and expects blind obedience.
Try to reason with her, she'll set her jaw and plant her swollen feet.
A female tourist doesn't believe in anything she can't clutch in her greedy little hands.
Possessing an idea, other than where your next meal is coming from, is as foreign to
this lady as the thought of you with another woman.
Security, even with a low life, is more important than her self-esteem.
She's easily depressed.
Running out of vanilla ice cream will cause a funk.
When down, she resembles a maniacal nurse and misery.
Yours may not be the greatest fan, but she's certainly capable of hobbling you
to keep you at home, not physically, but emotionally and financially.
She'll spend your money faster than you can earn it while investing
in her account, you'll never find.
She is a martyr. She blames the world, her job, the kids, and you for her own faults.
If she has four plates of lasagna, then it is ill later. It's your fault for letting
her eat so much. If she runs over a cat on her way to work, it's a cat's fault. It's
a cat's fault for being in the road. She's also a survivor.
Consider Russia's Catherine the Great.
Her family was duped into allowing an arranged marriage
with the heir to the throne of Russia.
When the prince turned out to be a half-wit
and Russia, a near barbaric country,
Catherine's mother protested the travesty
and was dispatched back home without a goodbye.
Catherine was 19.
Hate the great, not only survived, she thrived.
She used her earthly sensuality to screw her way
to the hearts of the prince's personal guard
and soon produced a bouncy and normal baby boy.
Rumor has it that the baby's father was a Cossack guard didn't matter to people who had been subjected to the whims of a madman
Later with another lover's help Catherine sees power had the evil emperor dispatched and saved the country she ruled for nearly 40 years
Galbraith the rest in a little bit. Yo, yes
Here's been a wild pow pow
What up be up without Tommy what are Arthur what up chat, what up?
Yeah, I'm just I've been I've been out the loop for a while to how to take care couple of shit you feel me
I was watching Tripp kick videos Paul one part two. I didn't want part three. That's a beating with the content
You know me. She always with the content
Shout to the shot. I'll see you with the content earlier. I had a tapper, you know, I've been out
Oh, how are you? How you been psyched in girl?
Not pretty good. God bless. God bless. And we have Arthur here saying say hi to you once again
Say man, I miss you brother. I miss y'all man. I start the bullshit. Yeah, you're what girl bye-bye
I miss you, man. How you doing there, bro? You don't miss me. You don't miss me Popeyes
I miss you man. Yeah, I've only been listening to clips shout out to twip quick
Shout out to trip kick shout out to beat beat
Shout out to Trisha. I be hearing you
I've been hearing you lately a lot you've been saying um
My face now. What's that dude? That's like paralyzed and now he's like shitting on everyone saying the n-words go
Oh, you know, you know, I didn't even cover that whole thing got it
Oh
Nobody nobody have that whole live like what nobody covering that I gotta come back to cover it like nobody got the log
Nobody clipped it. I gotta cook that man. I gotta cook it. I got the whole shit
He was while away while his wife was there. What I'm sassy scholar. Good morning threw me off was
When he was like, yo, I want to suck your dick and you were like, whoa, your wife is there. You didn't you never said no
make a
What what you know, you listen, I don't lie that fucking retarded suck my meat my nigga
Y'all niggas is fucking lame my nigga. I
Got to say no nigga
Is he want to suck my dick across the country why his fucking why his wife is there nigga, but I'm the gay one
I think he's looking for the dumbest shit my nigga. I'm not I'm not Momo, bro. I'm not Momo
I'm not Momo you're yeah, but you were never like nah, dude. I don't do that shit. You were just
How you want to suck my meat your girl right there shit is
I'm surprised. I got more caught nigga. I got the whole life. He went he went in for like an hour
And oh his wife was like making excuses for him to oh he needs the incident but that's the only thing he got
See, we didn't even get to cover that
I do feel bad for him, but he's been crashing. I don't feel bad. I don't feel bad for nobody nigga. I ain't gonna hold you
I don't feel bad
No, I don't feel bad, but you don't feel bad for himself
He's wasting his second life on the internet nigga Spazinaros in the hard art and nigga
He thinks he's winning with your trolling nigga. You ain't winning shit nigga
I'll go cover it. I might go live today. Nobody covered it. I might go live today and just cover that and she was going on
Come back and shit
What's been going on lately though besides that?
I'll be right back, but I haven't seen you around man
I really haven't been calling in as much shout out to Kate for holding it down during the summer
You know without her streams in the morning. It's been really slow. Psyche hasn't been going live as much
And when he goes go live though, he doesn't go live like he used to used to be late
Everyday I have every day. I've been for the 60 hours of that
Breaks you don't go live right back to back. Oh shit. All right. I'm mad here. I'm out of here. I'm out of here
later later later
You're always good to hear you for Tommy, but I mean it's always a fucker. That's the G right there. You heard call her
Yo, I had to interject on this gum a shit. Listen, I had no idea that it dawned to this level
But I was bored. I had a little free time and I went and I looked on his page
And I watched a couple of his last live streams and I was fucking almost damn near shocked
him sitting alone with one viewer bringing me and you up mainly me every every five fucking
minutes every couple minutes saying the weirdest shit there's gonna be blood he's gonna come up here
there's gonna be feds knocking on my door he's gonna come he's getting wild with it bro
We're bully and like we're out. He thinks I'm out to get he like thinks I'm working with people
And we're like out to get him and it's some big thing to get his disability taken from him and
You know every everybody's ganging up on him. He's like trying to do this victim shit, dude
I don't troll him. I don't follow him around. I haven't even been around Sam and
I know that's a fact it just and it's crazy because I got the last live his what his wife was on
Was on on a panel with him like oh no, I saw that I saw that with yeah with I need a
Yeah, I cut it in half
Yeah, yeah, I didn't get to cook it. I gotta cook it
I got I think I got to re cook it play from the beginning but it goes on yeah
He pick it off. He needs to answer that he needs this and the way he treats her my nigga you be shot
Y'all me too. You saw him in the fucking kitchen when it showed him on his little walker
We're fucking Walker my nigga in the fucking kitchen
Seriously this fucking this guy
The dude, it was you were on the panel with him.
I don't know if you saw it, but.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, no, I saw him on the, I seen him in the lip.
I think it was in the lip.
I think I thought I didn't know it was the kitchen.
He's totally, he's like, look at me.
His wife had his phone for him.
His wife had the phone and it showed him.
He's all trippin', he's all trippin'
on his walker in the kitchen.
Like he's gonna come and like come through the phone.
you get me and said shit like that. I'm gonna come through the phone.
There's gonna be more knocking on my door. You better do this. You better do this.
I was scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her.
I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her.
I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her. I'm scared for her.
My for I knew it on call my for phone call
But yeah, I think he hit yo Sam and I think he hits her hundred percent. Ain't no way you're not telling me
He gets that aggressive on a camera. Tell me ain't no way
I'm not judging her like I'll try to shout out to beat after it was gonna be this man
I'll try to tell be the we not tell we not jump on her, but she cannot make excuses for that nigga
He's a grown-ass man
But oh he needs to enter and he needs there's no he don't that nigga need God
He got a second life. Yeah, I like how you said I like how you said it a minute ago
He's wasting his second life
Tripping out on the internet and it's not even on the internet
He's alone over there thinking we're out to get him and it's some big conspiracy dude. I haven't even been around
I don't fuck with I was almost scared. I'm not gonna lie watching his he's obsessed with me
I watched a couple of his live streams and they're like an hour. He's obsessed with me. You too.
Come in and hit different. Come in and hit different. We had his back. Bro, we had his back.
We're not gonna keep do keep doing the bullshit and you doing way though shit to towards us and doing way though shit
We go call you up and you mad that we called you out. We're not kissing ass
We're not that's our timing. I agree with that because me and you we defended him shot to you
You use a big scum a supporter and I was like, you know, I don't I don't yeah
I let him kill so many of my people. He was always around before his thing and that's why he was kind of cool
He was a way different person and and I'm just I'm trying to give him grace because oh they're changing his meds
He is brain damaged. Yeah, I mean it is what it is, but yes, you're gonna be online
I'm gonna call you out for it and he's like yelling that whoever's around you're letting the cats out and tripping out
Like you might have to I'm not a clipper, you know, I'm not a recapper. I'm not a clipper
But yeah, some of that shit some of that
I'm just like, you know, yes, some of the shit from his last live stream
I think the very last one or the one before it's like an hour and he brings me up every 15 minutes and
But I just wanted to say what's up, and yeah, how do you talk? Oh, yeah, I'm living life. Dude. I was gonna say man
I'm good like I literally
I couldn't pass the background check because of the blogger thing. It was showing that I was charged with
You know the assault the assault and harassment or whatever
um
Well, anyway
That's gone now. It's been a year and they got rid of it
They said because I that was the deal with the court if I didn't get trouble for a year
It was deferred or whatever if just said they deferred it. Yeah, god bless
Don't get in trouble for a year. It's gone
I can pass background checks. I ain't gonna be a cash.
And there's nothing wrong with being a cashier or washing a dish or any of that.
A job's a job.
But, uh, no, now I'm like, dude, I can pass background checks again and get jobs and like, you know, the hospital or wherever, dude, and I'm actually going to sign new paperwork for a new place I'm working now, like, I'm not going to say anything more than that.
I just got my background in my drug test back. I'm good to go. So I'm excited.
Uh, I passed all of that and I got this job dude. Life's good. I am working a lot
That's why I'm not around but then that's why I was amazed with this scum shit
I'm like dude Sam, man ain't even been around. I ain't even been around and you're obsessed
Scum a you're obsessed man
He needed to read the fucking Bible man. Oh
We're always second life. I like that
Shout to the homies RIP nigga. I had a ticker out of nigga. I got real shit going on nigga
It's the summer you already know how it is. It's a summer niggas is dropping
I got to make sure my people's are good. I didn't fall back and these people wasting ain't lies
I see niggas lose their life for the dumbest shit and these niggas wasting any lives on the incident
Then they don't hit the same it's got me
He got a blessing on off to a second life and what you do trolling people. Hey, do you what you got to do Papa?
Don't get mad when niggas call you out on it
Exactly exactly and it is what it is like, you know
Fuck this shit should be for a laugh when it gets to be that bad
And like I said with his wife you aren't wrong. He yelled be yelling at her
There's a bunch of shit from when they were on the panel you do might have to run through that again him on his little walker
I mean, that's a right there. Tell me tell me I got I think I got when I was playing it
My my panel was crazy. So I didn't really get to cook. So I'm gonna play it through all through it out
Because I there was so much out to be there. I was on be this panel because that's why I fuck up be the
Because you get you get
Yeah
Oh, definitely wild shit
But I was just gonna say I was just bored when I clicked on his page and saw his couple live streams and watched them
They're like dude, he you're I think you're brought up a good amount to on some something
Yeah, well check you over your stream man. I hope you have a good day man. I do got to get going but go
day you guys
Nice to see you around Sam and I'll see you all the time. God bless you. Nice to see you Tommy. Yes, sir
I'm far far away. Thank you. Say nifty
That's it a biggest nickel in this section you're a neighborhood
Like where you so quiet say I got I was reading
Um, this one is called the it's called the comp day de gabales, and it's about
guy that uh
He went to where it was alchemist and the guy who taught him all about the elementals and stuff like that
Real quick the same man, I don't know if you knew but Kate's live right now brother, okay, and you told me because
Don't know you guys usually like hang out over there. Okay, they go see that's what I hate see you said I'm gonna do that
Have more respect for sight nigga
Well, he took my model way, you know
All right, but have more respect my nigga. I wouldn't even do that, bro
They started shit. I won't even do my nigga have more respect for sight. See I'm on I'm never like yo
I'm all I won't do that to psych especially on panel, bro. Now. He knows you love me. You know, he loves me. I love
Look at my name. I'm promoting shit
Why you not by over kite? I mean Kate
Cuz that's why I said you you're usually over there
Nice
Look, look, look at me there. You see me where I'm at beta. I'm over here, baby
How you been psyche?
We're gonna take the link. I need to talk to beta. No, no, no, she's gonna curse at you again, bro
We have a new guest on the show guys, we have a new guest here. All right, our new guest. Hold on this guy
He is a Brandon Looney Tunes hola
Oh, no, I know this guy.
This guy loves how you came over here.
He joins all the time.
He said you're okay.
Then open panel live in the search bar.
No, he's good.
Like, like, you don't need to block him.
He's good.
Okay.
So you're, you're, I think you've seen him before.
I kind of remember you.
Yes.
He's a good guy.
He's been here before.
Yeah.
Yeah, right. So there you go.
My favorite one is a Bugs Bunny.
Yeah, well, this is my original
avatar. Alright, you know,
take the link. Bita, take the
link. Save me. Go ahead.
I'll put my channel right here
in the public chat. Okay.
Next time next I don't need next I don't need a dollar and then you say could put it in the chat for you
Yeah, many people say I have the best channel
I'm nearly so off Louis tunes
You get a little Asian yeah, you get fruit for motion if you become a member you're
Yeah, I'm trying to get the 5,000
Subscribers good
Sorry, he does this on every panel. Shout out to you. I'm going on new panels a lot more
Yeah, you put to promote. Yeah, I see you Papa. Do you do what you do Papa? I miss the way to triple G
He's not like blackout
666 or something
Okay
Oh, okay. Okay. Come on up. Oh here's be here. What's that guy?
Yeah, you
Come back come on come back leader
You did come back
Everybody everybody go to Katrina's channel. It's cool. It's cool Katrina's cool. Yeah
We know I like I like Sponk Sponk. I like Sponk sponky. She's coming around sponky. She's sweetheart. Yes. Yes
Oliver yeah, I'm leeching Oliver
Yeah, Oliver there's my current avatar right now
Oliver oh, yeah, that's buddy here y'all you sit on panels you look stupid
Stay you Oliver. Stay you look beautiful
And that's my coming at the toy
Okay, that's awesome you're you're the rabbit
Username added
Are you the name as we add it?
I mean, am I gonna add it? I don't know. I'm not that big of a buggy funny fan, but you know
What's up doc? Yeah, what I what I'm a ruin
Puppet chat
What's the pup what's the puppet chat? Oh, yeah
Yeah, I got it. I got it. I
I got it. I got it. I got it.
All right, you know what? I can drink if I want to but I am
Well see what I'm gonna do is take a challenge because I do like a challenge
I'm not being stubborn, but I also think you're coming from a good place
So it's like I can do I can do panels still like I can be
I don't want you to stop me that that shit is hilarious. I was just joking Joe. Be the you will grow
You got no kids
Live your life. Yeah, but I'm still gonna keep my back because if I break it then you're gonna be like see I told you so
Nah, I'm a trip get covered there. I don't even I was out the loop for a while how to take care of shit
You know life is life, you know, well, uh, I
Shout to nobody cover that scar man. That's coming on your panel was that was a cookup and I showed my dad
Um, you know the video
I was like he's like who is that on the panel like you and bronze bird and Trisha and I'm like he's like
Oh, those are good people. They had your back like yeah, you know
I go live that was dangerous you didn't probably
Understood the danger of what you when you chase the guy. This is my current avatar right now. That was dangerous beta
You just like my natural instincts was like what the fuck like a third time
I just want to know who he was where he was coming from and get his information
You know, yeah, but be beat us once I've seen because I just came in I wasn't watching all and then I'm like
Why would a delivery guy show you we but I know how you are beta people in New York
You would have got eight up be the you would have got eight up already people who took you already you got
I'm talking have respect for the panel. Thank you. I appreciate that so be the
When I said you was good you was good to he probably smelt the weed. He was dancing. He was Lolli dog in you're doing your thing
He probably said oh, I'm like I could take advantage of this situation. Why would he show you weed anyway?
He's a delivery. I think I think he figured that he was like 33 dollars in so he might as well come over and bring some weed and
I've never had that happen, ever.
Usually people will just deliver something and leave, you know?
And no disrespect, Bita.
You weigh like at least 110, 150 pounds.
You're very light, Bita.
No, no, I weigh like 135 now.
All right, 135, OK, with the intro.
Bita, deep people command hand.
Ensure.
I was scared because nobody's around
and you live by yourself.
That's all I was saying. Go ahead. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, it was scary. I'm glad your ex. What's your ex? What's your ex?
What's your I didn't even fit it. What's your ex thought about this
situation? Because I know he came. He was like, he was pissed. He was like,
this isn't normal. Why are you fucking like, you know,
YouTube not support side by side ads.
And you have one month that swings the video player during mid-boss.
My god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god, my god.
So he was pissed it was like, you know, what the fuck are you doing?
Like these people are crazy. They're like, why do you like even get on the internet and talk to people?
I told you, Bito, plenty of times you should take breaks. I used to watch you. I'm like, damn, like last summer
I'm like, damn, Bita's not around. Damn, because I know she takes summer breaks. Now you're not taking you you you're not taking breaks
You keep maybe maybe
I don't know what it is. Maybe, you know, people got the lows at highs and lows, but
Every time I am trying not to do it. It's like somebody will stay shit. So I'm like, okay, I'm gonna go and defend myself
Yeah, and that's not I'm wrong with that be the you do what you gotta do. Nobody look your your panels be popping be the
I was looking forward to your panel last night and
Yeah, cuz I had to go somewhere and then I came back and like went to sleep, but
I'll go live probably tomorrow. All right, let me know just you know, let me know
Yeah, that's you be that like because you bring you bring other people
People don't the people don't go on other channels go on your channel and we could shit
We could shit talk we could cook it up. We could chill relax, you know
Yes, we go look at it papa. We got you
We're all gonna go we're all gonna go to the Looney Tunes Brandon's website you can
So I see he wasn't a drug dealer. He had like a little jar of little like popcorn nugs and a little bit of shake
Well, I had like an Alice in my house, you know, he definitely wasn't a drug dealer
Doug you don't you don't need a top. You don't need to tell me what to do though. You're fucking weird. Oh
You be saying old nasty shit nigga. I don't even know how you're around in church nigga. You definitely not allowed in my shit nigga
I ain't got hold and my channel is mr. Triple G wait in you say that nasty shit nigga dick
I don't be catching you nigga. I don't fuck with you nigga
You could suck you could suck the tip nigga and kiss it kiss it goodbye exactly
Fuck you telling me what to do nigga
They only go to 5k
Go get black. I hope you do. All right. Good luck. So be that so
Yeah
So what what's been happening besides that? I'll update you on the letter like a stuff that you know
Just like update you. Yeah
Good luck. You stupid getting calls though. Can I ask that or no? You don't want to talk about that. No, actually, no
True you show a trip kick I ain't good at trip kick show you so much love be that you yo
He had the best intros for you
He ain't got the good shit to like he gets he gets to the good parts I give him that
Yeah, that's he edits a dog thing and everything too. Yeah
Beep-beep-beep good to be people. Yeah, I love beep-beep. You know that that's that's my nigga beep-beep
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
He joined Psyche's apparently last night and freaked the fuck out of Psyche.
What?
I mean, it was weird, yeah.
The Ted Kennedy was weird, but Trump was okay.
Trump was pretty funny.
But he left up for a few minutes.
Maybe they couldn't hang.
Interesting.
Everyone was just screaming about something.
I was just like, it was just really so crazy.
Everybody likes him though.
Everybody likes the Trump character.
He's pretty good.
Yeah.
It was entertaining.
KZ you are fucking lame. I don't know why people listen KZ go back to Jimmy and they're gonna go back to suck a Jimmy dick
My channel my channel is triple G rated
I got you
G stands with general audiences always the minute
Yeah, but again like um, yeah, I mean I don't know none of my business
Maybe we were just going back and forth blaming, but you know, whatever
Doug you just started to talk shit. He wanted me to go at Kate right now. Clap Kate. He's telling me to go
clap Kate
Gotta you gotta you gotta understand me that's so
My child is my child is where you have any coastwoods too much
So maybe that something is that these are new all to just start us stir shit up
You gotta know when who's what and what's what?
You dig
you dig
Shit, I gotta go you guys. I'm like freaking six percent good talking to you salmon if you go live
Let me know and
Thank you
Keep up the good work
I'll see you guys. Have a good night. Good night. Good night. Sweet art. Bye.
Alright, Bita. Let me take it away. Shout to you, Bita.
Yeah, you can't clap me. I'll put up, I'll put up my, uh, here's my leg. Oh, I took it down already.
Yeah. Well, yeah, yeah. Let me do the claps with some guys. You know about it.
We just mentioned the chat. So how are we doing?
All right, okay
Yeah, that's just how you fix it. Oh, you still got the same rules
I think I'm just gonna do the uh
The you know the one time it's just there's just there's some ban for the day. It's not gonna be you can't buy yourself
Yeah, it's gonna be it's too much you could try and vast
You could try best say as somebody vests themself up. They can get
I'll give him a chance as some people are hated a lot I'll give them I'll give people a chance to bust them up
Now now if they get clapped before they get vested then they get clapped
But if you get vessel before the cloud then you stay on Pam
That's so good. That's that's the next fair the way to do it. Hey, hello. Yeah, I just
You know, I've had a pretty interesting panel today. Okay. I kind of like this been like kicking people off
Instead of like we're waiting for other people to do it. So I mean, it's like so I
Mean, yeah, that's one night. That's when it gets wack when people being wait for the night
You I let the content content and she happens. She happens. It's gonna happen naturally
Yeah, oh, here's here. Here's my
No, never mind putting it down putting it down. Okay, so that are you sneakers they say man. Oh, yeah
Who's that? Who's that person?
Yeah, sure. I don't know
And you pin it that's not a great
It
Oops, I think honey. Oh, oh, you stink you look at Kanye West. I mean
Gordon that's it a cat shout it to the cats and shout it to the cats out there, man
Say hi Samman. Oh, that's a beautiful cat
Hi, baby
I'm gonna give myself a cat on my birthday site
You are oh
I hope you're I think that you'll be very happy and
I
Congratulations
Go me everything or the shelter or the pet store. No, I'm going to a shelter
Casterly love man. There's a lot of cast out, you know
Yeah, that's you in New York City. Oh
I want to count with a story, you know, give me a story
not about
I'm probably getting me a little sicklet for my neck tend to need to update my fish tank
To be a nice or probably a flower horn or anything. Do you get those like edible fish at all or no?
Which means hell no
Like I mean the ones that are like I mean they're not the edible, but they're like they are the eat other
Yeah, yeah other people uh the other fishy. Uh, no, yeah, I got I got I raised a plateau from two inches to like
15 inches. He's so huge now. I got a
Kind of fish like that. It's a armored catfish. It's called basically a armored catfish
Uh-huh. I got a black neon. All right, you know, if you if you go to the past shop, right?
You see these staples, you see the goldfish and you see these blue and red
blue and red neons. It's like tropical fish, but I got the black version and I got the black version and I got the green top version
I like ice. I used to cut like fish, but it's a hassle because once you, once a temperature
change in your water, a little mistake you do in your water tank, it's over for your
fish. So you live or learn with fish. You're going to lose fish.
Yeah.
Like, when I first got into the hobby, I had a whole female beta tag, like, with seven
betas.
Females don't fight each other.
Do your homework.
Only males fight each other.
But females might get aggressive, but you got a lot of plants.
You could keep two male betas, too, together, if you got natural plants around.
I'm just kidding. Okay
Yeah, be no fish
Yeah, well, that's like in my in my song. It says like it's like a little error. You know, but it says yeah
it says like I
Mean a bunch of them. I'll play them soon, you know, but I've been playing them a lot like I've been doing the AI stuff
The AI music it's pretty cool
Pretty fucking good quality
Uh, I could call these it's pretty surprised. We have
It's for that pretty decent. Oh shit. Here it comes to down
Okay, these fish will keep growing as big as the environment's left down. I don't think that's how fish work
I think fish live in
I think they get as big as they're in the next day. I don't know. Oh what fish?
Yeah, okay, these educated
Go fish do that go fish as long as you they go fish to grow as big
Oscars you probably Oscars
Flower horrors. No flower more everybody got it
Shout to them all
Yeah, I'll work out the mall. It's like you want you want a discount. I got I got it
discount
This person's license plate license plate covers
What do you sell there?
The Senate's a sit-in button place
So we
Coke crack and that PC. Oh, please
You lie
You lie you lie. Oh my god. What up niggas? What up? Oh, I don't even know that niggas like a new odd trying to heal like
On my dick niggas. What up? Oh, stop it. You already know niggas
Not new niggas just slopping on my job
For no reason like
Remember I see that
What I don't know you never did that what?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
It's a third on Thursday on my show. Okay Thursday Thursday Thursday show
Yep. Hey man
Good morning
No, I just tapped it, you know, check in, you know, it's been a while. You gotta take care of my shit
Shout to you. That's a beautiful journey. I'm probably be back later
You're gonna be live by the time I get back for full. Yeah
Thank you
Love you to the chat to the chat much love later
Okay, oh my gosh clean up the sink that was oh wow finally got it clean. Okay. Wow that is crazy a lot of stuff in there
I'm just gonna give it a little Brits over here. Well, it's empty. Okay
And
Sorry my log. Hey, what are you doing, babe? Here's Lola Lola's
Come and hang it out with me. So how are you guys?
My sound for a little bit while longer right now. I'm gonna go stand maybe I'm getting a
Bagel with like and a coffee sounds really good right now. I'm not fall. I'll go alone
Hey, babe, I don't watch my hands. I'll be right there. You finish up
Yeah, I don't know. I guess like there's a lot of
There's a lot of
Stuff going on the media right now. It's kind of scary. So it's like, you know, that's why people may be freaking out in their normal lives because
It's like as above so below and
Things are
Going wrong in the world
We can tend to
Look a little crazy in our life. Okay. Okay. There we go
Hands wash down there
Okay
Right there
Oh
Good morning. Hi
The boss. Hey guys, so if you'd like a reading right now, you know
If you'd like to buy a more detailed read or like you'd like to buy one that I do it for free, so
I'll do a short one for anybody that wants one for free and then I'll
Longer one good morning
I love you guys. This one's for you guys.
For you. People losing it? Yeah.
That'd be the first thing.
Congratulations to
Ah, Marcy Fox got a free membership.
Congratulations.
You just received a free membership
to Second Awakens Tarot.
Marcy Fox, friend of the show.
Awesome.
Hey, there you are.
Oh, no, I thought I was her talking now,
which is, you know, but she'll get a membership.
She'll get an email about it, so.
Yay, Marcy got it.
Hooray, hooray.
So.
But I meant 93 I think I think I'm at 93 members at 91 so I just it's you so if anybody
Got any eight more and then I'll be at
100 I'll get more emojis guys. We haven't seen the emojis are so cool. Yeah, I'll show you look have a bunch of them now here
There's like 13 I think
They had like I need to reduce the skull I think that here the evil eye
Okay. Oh, you think it's short reduce monkey? Okay. Absolutely. You grab my cards
The Alice the cars are calling this morning
Okay, AOL
Yeah, I was just a classic. I was like
13 14 years old. I remember. Yeah, I got my first computer. I was like probably sixth grade
Didn't have the internet then I basically got the internet a little bit after that. Hey, well, they had it
Other stuff. Oh, these cars are good. Oh, I like to shuffle these cars
Okay
Okay.
Eight of cups, 10, okay.
Desmond's okay, okay, okay.
Oh, okay, that's good, okay.
So, spunky is what we have here is, okay,
we have the eight of C cups, okay.
So we have the eight of C cups,
and it's in the reverse, okay.
Eight of C cups in the reverse, okay.
So, you know, eight is usually,
that usually comes from kind of strength of emotions.
In the reverse, it's gonna,
It's gonna
Hopefully not be too negative
It says that
There's like some kind of indecision right
And then it's like there's some kind of there's certain relationships
And I don't think it's your I don't think it's a romantic relationship
I think no every friendship at the tipping point and you're not sure whether to walk away or keep trying fix the bonds
So it says use your intuition instincts even if your mind is having trouble
We had to benefit some pitfalls your heart knows what to do. Okay, so
But I have that then I see that
We have like this kind of hedgehogs a set of hedgehogs is like the kind of pentacles, right? That's like the
Really good really good cards. There's a really good generational. So it's like it's something
weird did happen with somebody
It looks like everything's gonna work out for the best, but
this ten of a pentacles
You know, that's what ten of cups ten of pentacles is what everyone wants. They want the
Long-term happiness the ten like the ten right?
So I'll go out of the book for you for this and of hedgehogs says
Head of Hedgehogs represents accumulated wealth, satisfaction, and sustained success.
You worked hard and now are seeing the resulting comfort and stability.
Tarot card is also symbolized as a happy stable home and supportive family, which is always
a good thing.
Okay, and then judgment is being called.
For something so I don't know if something was just made fair again for you
But yeah, so it looks like there's some kind of judgment being called, you know justice always falls to the judgment
It was unfair. There's a nice little rabbit, too. I don't know the rabbit may
You might like the rabbit is he kind of stands out to me in this one
You know, I'll tell you about the judgment card
Judgment always comes December 20. It comes right before
The justice comes
And so it says, when the white rabbit blows his trumpet
to announce the arrival of the queen of hearts,
the tarot card judgment announces the arrival
of an important realization.
Judgment marks the time to make amends
for past blunders or wrong doings and forgive yourself.
So everyone makes mistakes, that's a simple nature of it.
Whether you've heard someone's feelings,
made a poor judgment call,
found yourself late for an important date,
judgment encourages you to make amends and forgive yourself.
Right?
And oftentimes it's, yes, we're toughest on ourselves too,
but it's a judgment, right?
But oftentimes it's gonna be,
maybe called another people.
They're called, it calls for us all though.
You've come so far along the journey
and grown so much along the way,
it's time to leave regrets and guilt in the past
and move forward.
Okay.
And finally, we have the five of wands,
which is the five of flowers,
you know, five of wands,
It's in the reverse though. So you lucked out, right?
Because you know usually by a lot of fighting and there's people I mean there
Sometimes it looks like they're having fun, but there's pity to ever sticks and stuff like that
But this is about kind of a advice. I think it was released to avoid confrontation
I think in your okay, so it says are you avoiding this or or maybe not avoid it because
If you can fight it if you can easily fight it
But it's like if you're avoiding one and see this it's time to stand up for yourself
Like the Alice as you chastise the red Queen during her trial
Everyone has their breaking point avoiding conflicts will only make things more explosive when you finally do say what's on your mind
So it's best to get it out and open sooner rather than later. Let's see advice for you. I mean, it's like I hope it makes sense
it's like
Yeah
Sometimes it's good to fight especially for yourself, you know
So stand up for yourselves and it looks like
You know defend what you have because it looks like that is our generational
Comfortability that comfort ability
Achieved you're welcome. Hope you liked it. My pleasure. Thank you. Party network
So Jim in the holograms. Yeah, Jim to the outrage is
Yes, yes, sir
Put on brother. How you doing psyche? We're in the building man. We're in the building man
You're in what I said, we in the building
We're in the guys in the building. Yeah, yeah
We're going to take you out. We're gonna go. We'll see if I'm not too bad. It's gonna see it's just been a little bit. Yeah
Doing pretty good. I've you know finished off my eliminated
You know I had a nice night on yeah, well, it's a hard lemonade. It's a harder harder lemonade
I'm just shaking it very slowly. It's not uh, it's not Mike's hard lemonade. Is it?
Yeah, it's harder Mike's harder lemonade
I've actually never I've actually never had that I just knew I
Don't know if Chris Hansen show was like promoting it
Or something like that you remember that show right? Yeah, you know to catch the predator to catch a predator. Yeah, but I
Do you remember that I used to say I remember these to say hey, I got a soda and some pizza
The woman was like a 13-year-old boy or something like that right and so yeah, the woman coming and
Yeah, that was quite a show the he-man the flash the Joker and
I don't know if they had a nice hard lemonade, but yeah, maybe it's only right
No, no, no, they did on the show. They did. Yeah, I remember. Yeah, I mean, that was it was 2008. I think that was like, you know, how it was like 17 years ago. Can you believe it already? Yeah. Yeah. No, that was that was the thing that they promoted was Mike's hard lemon eight, which again, like I said, I've never had it.
Right. That's all they kind of
That's like the thing they would use on the show with the decoy. She'd be like, oh, can you can you get some mics hard lemonade?
All right, like every shmuck every shmuck. That's what they say to him
I never I never remember I don't remember that but yeah, I'm sure they probably did Murray I baked the brownies
Yeah
Hi
Those guys in that show were kind of they had they had some real funny ones
Now we're are you seeing the guys on YouTube psyche that are making their own shows?
They're making their own to catch predator shows
Sure
Have you seen any of those there's a bunch of them going around?
Yeah, I've seen too. I mean it seems like they have this big a
Yeah, you know, they show up to you. He's at the door, you know, so
Yeah, so I remember a couple years ago. I
Was on this one guy's channel. He's he's more like an MMA channel makes martial arts and
We ended up, you know, it's kind of like your channel, right?
it's like your channel like we're a group and
You know, we had a couple of these guys coming in and start trolling us and we didn't think much of it
But they're like, oh, we're from this guy's channel, blah, blah, blah, right?
So I don't want to say the name just yet, but we end up going there and we find out
this guy, he's one of those channels where he's getting like 30 comments every second.
And the only comments that he reads are super chats and again, he's getting a super chat
I don't know every 30 seconds like crazy channel, right?
Well, anyways, they end up coming back and invading us with like a hundred two hundred counts
Anyways long story short that guy ends up getting caught as a petal
That channel I got was going on. Yeah, you want me to say the channel name he's known in the YouTube world
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yeah, well they had a guy on like on the show on the Predator show that he got he got like
Hot one night in the house, and then he was like anything they caught him like two days later the same guy
Yeah
But he was like he seemed like he was kind of retarded though
I mean it's like I mean some of the people were like, you know, some of them seem very slow
I'm not sure and remember the guy did on a live himself to like the lawyer guy and then they had to cancel the show because
It was like you because it was actually that that perverted justice, you know that organization, which is that I think it's you know
They are they were a little bit. Yeah, they were a little bit
Crazy in those chats, right?
They were pretty I don't know but they were very and they were very determined to get these guys
But it's like you had to follow the like the local local police laws
And it's like they didn't do it right and they just had to let them go and stuff like that
And they didn't do it right like a lot of time and because there was a thing so
So you need to like, you know, they need to do it carefully, right?
We need to get as much money he man and Johnny bravo, okay?
Yeah, it's yeah, well, that's the thing right like
You definitely have to follow with what the law says as far as if you're trying to get someone taken down because it's like
You know, even I mean if you think about it even the police themselves
They have rules that they have to abide by like they need warrants and shit like that
If they're ever trying to catch somebody so, you know, same thing goes for but yeah
I mean when you're talking how you just
Which you just referred to them as
That's the thing psyche like it kind of goes untalked about but majority of these people they they have mental health issues anyways
They're not exactly
How do I say they're not exactly the brightest in society?
and it's just like
Again, it's more than just a sociology problem. I like I said, it's a psychological problem like if someone
Is willing to do what they're doing like you know trying to get with a minor or whatever
You know, obviously, there's a lot going on. There's a lot going on mentally
Like it's a very dark world. It's a very dark world
But I think that it's like it's really
It's like I think that there probably could be like
Treatments or therapy that could be more like you know effective with it
But it is like such a thing that is like it is so
You know people are there's such a reaction to it and they're such as like, you know people over there
You know these people say basically Murph, you know, I don't live them right away, right?
People people are sheeps. That's the thing psyche people are sheeps
So what people do it like at the end of the day me and you come to an agreement that the the act of that is wrong
The act of it is not valid
You know, we would never condone it, you know, and we we would obviously advise no one to do it, but
But we're obviously, like I said, we're trying to get to the root cause of the problem, just like with anything.
And I feel like when a lot of people are like, oh, death to all paddows or the way to fix it is a gun to their head.
I kind of like, I just really start thinking and I'm like, okay, like I get what you're saying.
These people what they do wouldn't be good right like it traumatizes a child for life
But I'm like I really sense because I can pick up on energy psyche
And I really sense that with a lot of them are just sheeps
They're just repeating what they heard others say or they're just saying what they think is gonna make them be accepted in society
Like oh look at me look at me. I'm against it. So you guys are all gonna like I just I don't know how many of them are genuine
Well, they do you for me sake. Does that make any sense? Yeah, definitely
Especially now when there's like such an overused
accusation, I mean, it's like everybody like literally everybody
in
Chats in certain chats. I've been certain people that will call everybody that and it's like I think those people might have
Issues to sounds like he's defending them. Okay. Well, there's what he's saying is like
There should be maybe more therapy some maybe understanding of the root cause of it rather than I think that there's like actually an effort in society to promote
Okay, you know it's how they made those like weird shows on like Netflix with like the
There's like a beauty page and so now they have these like in these acts and it's like so there's all this like
Messages thrown out to people right in the media, right?
Not defending anybody if they could but it's saying
If the society is sick does that trickle down to the people? That's an example
Thank you that the person saying I'm defending them that that's a prime example of a sheep, right?
So that person if you really think about it, right?
I don't know who the hell they are right, but just think about it if they didn't if they didn't really hear what everybody else
Had to say about you know petals and whatnot would they be as passionate and I I really don't think they would be
You know what I mean? It kind of goes with the whole thing about like racism is taught
I don't know if you've ever talked to people with like
Disabilities and like autism and stuff like that if you ever talk to them
Right you might get once in a blue moon the one that can talk and they might be racist
But if you meet most of them like let's see
Some as far as a 90% of people with autism or actually I'll even go as far as say a hundred percent of people with autism
That can't speak that are non-verbal you will not find one of them. That's racist
Just because because of the disability and what they're able to interpret so they're not it if they grow over the racist parent
They wouldn't be able to inherit that they just can't right the only thing they're gonna know is
They're what they're learning ability allows them to which a lot of them they function at a kid's age
Like five years old or less than that
So that's what I'm getting at is a lot of this stuff. It's just
You know we see like here's a here's a fact well if somebody's on a list
Like the registered list there. I don't want anything to do with them
They're not they're not they're not coming in my house. They're never going near my children like that. That's a fact
That's why that's why they're on the list. They're on the list. That's what we're doing for that reason, right?
Exactly, right exactly and this person who's saying you're defending them right again
This way certain people are able to have intelligent
Conversations and certain people they can't they're just they're just emotion. They don't think what they're had they think with their emotions
And I people like that. I can't really help them
you know if they're too much in their emotion but you know like I said it's um
I think that person's one of them where you know um how much of an opinion would they form on their own
had they not saw us like such a strong community you know stand up to this crime you know but again
I I always just say this like I say this all the time psyche
I don't understand the logic in the prison
when these people killed innocent grandmas,
fucking beat the shit out of innocent grandmas,
but then when they go to prison, they're untouched,
but then they can go and beat the shit out of a guy
who touched a minor.
I don't get that.
So the grandmas not get the same fucking respect?
Like again, these people are,
Picking and choosing I think if you go to prison in my opinion if you're you guys are all in the same area then then you're all
Fucking the same thing you guys are all the same
That's another thing is like so many people that go to prison
With horrible crimes, you know, then they get a little bit of like a case of rehabilitation or whatever and like, you know, usually
If the crimes aren't too serious, you know, that's pretty pretty easy
but and so
You know, they think the prison is like
It's like it's like it's like it's actually a pretty effective effective way to go, but yeah, they
They I forgot my point exactly. But yeah, it is very uh, they are their protective custody usually a prison
But yeah, there's but they have it so would they go there get a little piece of rehabilitation and then they decide
Okay, well this person is he's a this the sin is worse like there's a worse sin or whatever right there's also the sin
But so but it's like people get very holier than now and it's like even people that have done horrible horrible things
They like they like they find is like a way to think it's a way to like get read redemption or something in the eyes of
people you know, I guess maybe
But uh, well, you know, it's interesting psyche, you know, you know
I just told you about those channels that are going around trying to be like Chris Hansen and
Yeah, there was there was two of them that I heard of
Two of them where they found out later on those guys were also pedos. So it was pedals
Pretending to go around catching other pedals
Okay, yeah
Yeah, it's like a projection the projection. It's like, you know, it's like people that are maybe the strongest about it
I don't know. There's like a lot of complicated things that even what causes that I would say, you know
Like a lot of people have this childhood trauma or something like that that they repeat the cycle or something like that
Or you know, I don't I'm not sure exactly what but it's like I think you know with all the
All the up for about it. It should be more more carefully studied and like really understood. I don't maybe maybe it is
There is a better understanding of it than some people have but oh, there is
Thank you. There there is and it's more amongst educated people, right?
Educated people people have degrees and whatnot. I'm not saying all of them
But it really depends on who you're going to these are highly educated people
I don't know if you you know if you go off to like let's say your chiropractor or
You know these people are not saying any of the crap that we hear on these channels like you know
I mean no offense to the people that come on here, but they're they're really
Like I don't want to say their opinion doesn't matter
I think everybody's opinion matters to an extent, but it's just a lot of times when you're coming with too much emotion and too much
Self-centered opinionated. I don't know how serious I can take you
Like it gets to a point where it's like all right, man. Like, you know, like
You know, let's be logical
Let's say some facts because it's like I've been talking to you for a fucking hour and you haven't said one fact like come on
Let's get somewhere. But you know, it's the YouTube world
Everyone's got freedom. I mean you you just have
You just had Brandon on here, right? I have to click the rewind and I noticed Brandon was here
Mm-hmm. Yeah, Brandon. Yes
You know Brandon who were is he is back at the guy the loonies who guy or no, no. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, so I've seen interesting guy
Yeah, I've seen here's the funny thing, right? So like it's like this is the logic you get with people
I'll give you a great logic. I've seen a channel. I'm not gonna say who that guy is, right?
But Brandon Brandon would go to this channel all the time and this guy
Was telling Brandon hey Brandon can you shadow box for us?
Right, which is just a boxing exercise and Brandon's like, okay, then the guy says hey Brandon
Can you take your shirt off? I'm not capping psyche this really happened and Brandon's like, okay
So Brandon takes his shirt off like just just a t-shirt and he starts shadow boxing, right?
And then later on that day some other guy
Tells Brandon hey Brandon. Can you touch your toes while you say run?
and that got the guy that told Brandon,
the guy that told Brandon to take his shirt off,
got so mad, got so mad over that and made a big deal
and said, you shouldn't be telling Brandon
to touch his toes.
And then the next day,
The next day he goes, again, he tells Brandon to take it.
So what I'm saying is I don't get to logic with these people.
This guy thinks it's okay to tell Brandon to take his shirt off.
But then he tells the other guy,
don't tell Brandon to touch his toes.
I don't, I don't, like I don't, they're obviously,
they're obviously both taking advantage of Brandon
because they could see that he's got autism, right?
They're obviously both mocking him.
But I don't get the logic how the guy telling Brandon to take a shirt off thinks it's okay
But what the other guy does it's not okay like it. That's why thank you
Like I said all these opinionated people that are not educated. I really don't give a fuck about what they think
Because it's it's just it's their brain. It's their emotions. It's their little fairy tale
Yeah, yeah, it reminds me of like in in narcissism. There's like stuff. There's a phenomenon called
leveling and it's where a narcissist will
Push someone down like push the one down to the level that you know make them all bad and put themselves up on a pedestal and say
But then they're all good and it's like because they when you because they they level themselves
They feel better about themselves because they're so insecure and stuff like that
They have to push somebody else down so they can be just always sure of their superiority. That's for me too. Hold on
So BSBV says he's talking about Chubo's chat channel.
He says grooming, okay.
Yeah, I personally, I'm not gonna say the channel name,
you know, because it's Psyche's channel
and I would never want to start a beef or another,
but yeah, sir, what were you saying Psyche?
No, no, no, no, yeah, yeah, I was just,
yeah, what I was saying was basically,
yeah, the people will level, they'll say,
oh, they'll put the person on a lower level, you know,
either by, you know.
just in their mind or, you know, telling that person they're on the lower level and then they'll
they feel leveled up. It's like they have to do that because they're kind of insecure about themselves
and so they have to feel better, feel like they're better than somebody. But even though we're all
human beings, we're all equal, we all make mistakes. The point is like
You know better yourself to change some people maybe need to go to mental hospitals be a medication. I don't know
I don't know the I don't know the answer. He's showing opinion right now and
And nobody cares. Is that any opinion? Well, that's okay. We can have opinions and share opinions
Well, they they they definitely care because if they didn't care they would leave you see how that works
So no, they definitely care, you know, it's just like even when I go live
I'll get I'll get the occasional trolls that'll just comment dumb crap or say, you know this and this and I'm like
Yeah, but you know, you're one of the 25 people watching me and
Yeah, exactly
No, it's all good. The best thing is I I could say what I want here
You're gonna you're gonna be forced to live. I mean, obviously I have an opinion like everybody else
What I'm saying is when we're gonna talk about social issues
If we're talking science
social issues
Anything to where you know, it's like a humanity thing. I think our opinions should get set aside and we should go with logic reason and
understanding and again
You're not going to do that if you don't have a base foundation of philosophical understanding, like you have to understand how to deal with things.
See, they literally, I don't know if this guy knows, they literally teach you this in the seventh grade in social science class that the kid who ends up joining a gang,
At a young age like 10 years old or 12 years old and ends up going to prison in and out of prison his entire life
They're gonna tell you that this guy had it worse than anybody because it you know
This guy wasn't really given all these opportunities that spoon-fed people were given
mm-hmm
You know you see what I'm saying now obviously can make me the the argument that even
People who had it better, you know, you know, it's not like they're spoiled. They still have to work for what they had
But again, you know, unless you take you get into social sciences, you're not going to understand the sociology issues that we face as a society.
And again, when people want to be like that and they want to be so opinionated, we're going to be selfish.
We're going to be selfish. Sorry, selfish. And we're not going to, we're not going to want to help one another.
That's, uh, and I think that's what we're ought to do. We're ought to really help one another.
Yes, I agree and I think that and we can and it's like, you know, some people may need to be you know, you know kind of like
Segregated a little bit from the from the main society, right? And you know
you know, it's like, you know, a
lot of people
I don't like a lot of people are just going crazy, you know, like they're I mean to people are just saying about everybody
There's people like, you know, we have the old satanic panic back in the 80s where they were confusing like, you know
women and wheelchairs old ladies the wheelchairs and the old preschool
Grandma's, you know, there's already imprisoned for years under this investigation
There's not one person was charged in the case after certain the most expensive one of the most expensive court cases in history
And they're saying that they're taking them on planes after school kind of same similar to the
EPSC and stuff where they're like, oh, yeah, they're getting on planes and flying around nobody realized this
All right, so this Bible study is no what I'm talking about the Bible. We're talking about you know
This is panic panic was something that was real it happened in the 80s at a preschool in California right where I live like right
So in California and they
All of a sudden they had the psychologist talk with the puppet to the kids and they in the puppet
It would talk until the child would say what the psychiatrists wanted them to say
And so they were bad with them basically you can see it all in the transcripts. You go study it. It's interesting
Yeah, I guess
Yeah, yeah, and then yeah, and also like think about the gang violence gang violence, too
is like, you know, it's like that is hurting innocent people that is like
You're putting drugs into the communities that is like, you know, and so there's a lot of like really negative things
Everyone has to like look at their own shadow, right? You know, it's like some under we're under world stuff goes on
Yeah, I'm sure it does it goes space. Oh
You know, but I my my
My experience in society psyche is that it's easier for one to point the finger at others
than it is to point the finger at thyself, and so it's like, you know, it's easier for
me to even just see a bunch of my problems and my insecurities in you before I see them
You know, that's really a fact because that's that's been my experience with people, you know
And I get it and I think I think it's a great way to start because here's what I think with majority of people
You're not gonna be able to
Get to know who you are and get to start the healing process
Until you start pointing the finger at others, right? And but here's what I'm saying
Maybe do it for a couple years like do it for a couple years and then eventually
Lead it to where you're pointing the finger at yourself, and then that's how you can help yourself, but some
Some are never gonna get to that stage
Some are just gonna keep
pointing it at everybody else
It just takes the ability to have like the insight, like self insight, you know, like to be able to do introspection and like look at yourself, and also like I will say there's something called shadow work and I don't know if you've heard of shadow work, but yeah.
And it's like and and the thing is everybody has a shadow and it's like and I think in the world today
Everybody is like, oh, let's go hunt down shadows
Let's go hunt all the shadows and they're not realizing that they have one too
And it's like their shadow is the same as the other person's shadow
It's like and so you know what a shadow is a lot of darkness a lot of stuff
We don't understand like a lot of things hit a lot of illusion, right? And so, you know
You know, I think the illumination is always the friend enlightenment. There's an understanding that happens there, right?
There's also, you know, people can change their mind.
Psychological stuff can be treated and healed often, you know?
It's just like, I don't know if we have all the answers yet about, like, a lot of mental
disorders or if we're treating them the right way, I think we over-medicate for certain.
you know, psychiatric things we have in the therapy is kind of still experimental in some cases, you know.
Interesting topic though, you know, it's interesting to think about and, you know, certainly with stuff going on in the world today,
it's important to have an understanding of, you know, not just like how everything's so secretive.
No, for sure, it's like, it's like, why, right?
Why keep, you know, mental health and all this like a secret?
Why, right?
It's a big thing for us to talk about.
There's a lot of shame there's shame in it. There's also I guess we're woefully unprepared to deal with what because you know
We basically criminalize the eventually ill instead of you know treating them a mental asylum
I think that goes back to maybe Reagan or something where you like you take all the site emptying out these silos and fill up all the
Prisons, you know, that's kind of like where we are now. We don't really have a great
mental health
Institution they just take them to prison now, right?
You know
That's the thing psyche right they started spending so much money on these
You know state-of-the-art prisons, you know, and I mean is it for the guards or is it for the prisoners?
Right like who is it for because you know the guards love it there, you know
It's like real nice for them, right, but um, maybe it
Yeah, you know the prison is like a lot of prisoners
It's really my prison because it's like, you know, it is like a
You know full these things like cats like camp for a lot of people, you know
I think the same most people miss is like the women or something like that. But yeah
It's your everything's paid for basically, you know, I think it causes it costs like a over
$100,000 a year to house somebody in a prison. I mean, they're just very very expensive like very expensive
You should say even they don't really yeah, it's a lot
They get paid to anything they hardly, you know, the prisoner Mary came in 30 cents a day, you know
Working full day that that sounds like slavery to me almost right
No, it is yeah, it is yeah, you know, it is and I think a lot of people have a
Harsh look on on when someone gets into crime and they say oh well, it's their fault
but it's this is why people are judgmental
psyche is because
See when we see things from the perspective of the most high and I mean obviously and all this time. I've talked to you
I know you have your very spiritual being
All these times I've talked to you psyche, so I know you have your own belief and
Who the most high is or God or whatever your interpretation is?
But to see things from that being's perspective the most high, you know the one above all
Is to be understanding of all humanity. It's just like I wouldn't going back to sociology problems
It's to understand that really the tunnel vision that the guy in prison had wasn't to
I don't know become a doctor a chiropractor a lawyer a psychologist a
Manager it's like the guy was lost in life. He was lost. He didn't really know what to do
He wasn't surrounded around like he wasn't surrounded around the best people like it really reminds me of the movie twins
You remember twins with Arnold. Yes, Arnold. Yeah
Schwarzenegger and DeVito, right? Right, right. So that movie Arnold grew up in like if you remember a nurturing loving environment and then and then
Danny Danny the short guy grew up in a very aggressive New York City hostile
Right, like we know in New York everybody's showing, you know, I'm driving over here. Get out get away from me
So it's like it shows you how the big guy who can choke out Danny like kill him with one arm
was a million times more loving and kind and understanding because of the environment he was in.
And again, I just think people...
Never take the time to show an abundance amount of gratitude for how good they got it instead
It's just like oh no, you know screw that screw that prisoner. It's always fault. You know
You should have known better. No, man
If you were in his shoes, you wouldn't never did it any differently
You wouldn't have done one thing differently if you were in his shoes, but and you know, that's all I preach to people. It's like
Be more understanding
Right, and I've also seen like a lot of documentaries about prison, and I've seen like
Prisoners not only like you really like open them up hard into like animals
They've taken raised dogs and cats and stuff like that. That seems like so many very talented
People like you know either talent there's gonna be the basic like culinary stuff. They keep you know, they're very creative
They're you know, you kind of like learn how to be creative there too because you have so much time and then so so few things, right?
So if you but it's like, you know, it is like a lot of pretty probably brilliant people that they put that if they were in a different
situation they might have put their
there are energy into like a legal the legal method and would have made you know even more you know
it's like there's sometimes people think crime pays it really does that if you consider like the uh
you know the jail time and the you know like uh
Collab you know there's like a lot of stuff that goes that's been a negative you know it's nice
You always have to you don't just like steal from people and it's like it's not doesn't affect like a lot of people's lives right so
Yeah, I mean I just saw a video of a I just saw them a video of a mule
she was a Mexican lady and
The cops caught her that I think they caught her it was in Arizona
She was she claims she was going to Pennsylvania
But they you know they it was just a random traffic stop and then you know like I how are you blah blah and then I don't know
They got the idea to let the canine out
and the canine started smelling the truck
and they're like, all right, you know, at this point,
we're gonna have to check out your truck.
It was just a moving truck.
She claims she was moving.
And they found over a million dollars worth of Coke
in the back of the truck.
And they actually gave her a pretty good offer.
They said, look, they said, look,
we don't really want you, you know,
and they're like, well, we, they're like,
what we wanna do is, if you're interested,
We'll set it up with the d8 where you'll deliver it to where you got to deliver it
And we're gonna get the other guys and they're like we don't want you at all
So, you know, they did try and get her to snitch pretty much, but um, yeah, man
Psychi if you watch her man, I'm telling your heart's gonna drop bro. She's like the
calmest
Most like humble lady ever like I really felt bad like she didn't give the cops any attitude
It was yes. No, like she had broken English and stuff
But I just felt so bad for her because it's like she goes like this. She's like oh my husband doesn't know I'm here
And then he's like, oh husband, she's like, yeah, I got a husband and three kids and she's like they she's like they think I'm
Because she used to be a mover. She had a moving company one of the movers
And she's like, oh, they just think I'm moving somebody's house right now. They don't even know I'm doing this and I just I mean
I just felt so bad bro. I felt so bad for the lady
And that's why they told you they said we don't want you but but here's the thing psyche
How how can how can she kind of like snitch on the cartel bro?
How can she snitch on?
Yeah, I know that's like that's gonna be the heart the heart thing right but that's yeah
It's because it was kind of like yeah. Yeah, go ahead. Thank you. Sorry sir for erupting. I know I just I don't know
You're not an update. I just feel like you know, it's like it is you know very
It's very tempting for some of these people to carry this bag across the border.
And it's like it's like some people might not even understand really what's going on
Like it's like so. Yeah, you know wait a minute a woman in prison forever
She's for a drug charge, you know, it's like when she was to do like, you know
But they do offer that deal to everybody our justice system is run on this on the informant system
That's how it's just one of the big things that keeps keeps it going right is like just continually informant
So there's also no honor among thieves, right?
Hearing past a matrix or what I don't know is a T why you're being everyone's being kind of like hard on this guy
He's like he's just you seem very reasonable to me. You seem like you're
Just out yours
I'll tell you what it is. I'll tell you what is
You're always gonna have jealous people like you're good. So here's what the human mind loves to do, right?
Soaring human minds when they hear intelligence it drives them nuts because they think to their self
Oh, man, you know, why couldn't I sound like that? Or why can't I be that intelligent?
So I don't I don't really like you gotta remember I've been on YouTube for like decades
I've been on here for decades and I I can pretty much I
When you know, they don't have a social life. That's why they want to cut you off all the time
I want that's why they want to be the the center of attention. Those are all signs for
Not being social enough. There's nothing wrong with it. There's I'm not I'm not making fun of it. I'm just
I'm just awkward. No awkward. They're awkward, right? Yeah. Yeah, yeah
Like you just you could tell that their social skills isn't the best, but it's it obviously has to do with like I said
You know not talking enough in the public
Sorry, I'm just kind of doing a little bit of chores while I'm talking here right now
Yeah, yeah, but it's
I got no problem. I got no problem with the haters. We call them troll babies or I'm from we just call them troll babies
So good. Yeah, but the troll babies troll
So someone's asking someone that's in the chat asking you what's your opinion about people who docks other people's underage
You know children on YouTube out of spite. Have you heard of people that do that?
Yeah, so that I haven't seen that. Yeah, and that's even more dangerous. It's doing you know, it's like
Yeah, I don't know
It's definitely wrong it's definitely like here here's always been my opinion as a you know as a youtuber as someone who comes here all the time
If if right now me and psyche get into it, and I'm like, you know f you and he's like f you you're an idiot blah blah blah
I feel like that's one day like one day is one lifetime
So we ended today and if tomorrow if he doesn't want to talk to me and he wants to keep it
We keep it up there. I'm like I respect your wishes
But the way I believe it should be done is I believe we should both be emotionally intelligent say all right
Let's start fresh today
But we we just leave it on the white on the on the YouTube. We never
Take it to the personal we never get
Like like I mean forget about forget about psyche's family. I'll never dox him
So let alone his family like forget about his family. That's out of the question
It's the question is about him and home never get done
Anybody that I go off that will never get done. So I think I think that's how people should be so
and
Then someone saying JC saying we have the ourselves the arbiter of morality here
Well, you know what? I see a lot of arbiter the morality
I'm just saying a lot of people that are just like holier than that. Hey piranha. How are you?
I see a lot of holier than now people that are like, you know, it's like we forget we're all human beings, right?
And it's like we're
You know, we're just human beings. We're all for imperfect flawed
Hopefully we don't hurt anybody that you know, that's why I wouldn't just get out of this life
That is never never causing harm to anybody indirectly or indirectly, you know ever, you know, that's like that's well
Well psyche these people
These people don't understand we're being watched every minute, and I'm not talking about on the internet by the government
I'm talking about
by source like but by the ones that source has
power to watch us whether it's like whether it's spiritual guides whether
it's certain type of spiritual beings out there like you know I don't pretend to
know everything about the spiritual realm and all that goes into it but I know
we're being watched at every minute I know our thoughts are being monitored I
know our actions all of that and I like before we get into actions before we even
get into
Oh, you know, let's not go outside and throw a rock out of house before you even talk about the action. The thought alone, I believe is documented and in a way like I'm not saying it's going to get used against you.
Because, you know, like my belief when you die, I don't think you're going to be judged
the way they say you will be.
I think you're just more going to be shown how you could have did it better, so to say.
But any who, yeah, I think it'd be the thought alone, like you could almost get questioned
on, you know, why are you having bad thoughts or demonic thoughts like, oh, let me throw
a rock out of house.
I think I think that should be like that's why we really got to pay attention to everything our thoughts
Where we are spiritually mentally
Because some of our thoughts might not be our own necessarily right
Or they could I think I know we have your responsibility for our thoughts, but there are
Thoughts that are implanted and people's heads are suggestions. It's not called a power of suggestion
That is very very very powerful
Especially if you use like in them in an evil way, which is a lot of people do they didn't evil way
That's what predictive programming is, you know with the movies and trying to get these scenarios to happen and on the earth
There's these really terrible scenarios. They're not like happy scenarios. They're always
These terrible scenarios, right? And so
Right we really do focus on the negative this order of chaos things to you
It's like, you know, it's called all this chaos and you know
There's one thing it's like people who emerge out of the desk from it, but I think we should like all realize
Let's all like, you know
Hey help each other out. It's human beings, right? We are human beings
So I know yeah
People would never go out of the middle school bullied mentality true. Yeah
Yeah, I mean when you talk to that thought thoughts not being hours if you're referring to
Like the devil himself, then yeah, I I know that
That individual that spiritual being
Can influence thoughts in our head because I'll tell you this here's when I realized this being
Here's where I realized this being is so disgusting
The the more you get closer to the most high
And that, you know what your purpose is and you're trying to change the more he continues to mess with you and
I've achieved like I'm I'm still kind of going through it to be honest where it's like a tug-of-war battle
But ultimately I keep drawing to the source to the to the most time
And so I just you know just to add on pick you back what you're saying how they're not our thoughts at times
You're a hundred percent correct. And that's why we need to so the way the way I say it is psyche
It's like a radio channel, right? Imagine you're in your car
You could put on any channel you want channel 955 channel 107.2 blah, blah, blah
so we want our frequency to match with
The most high with the good the good spirit being our spiritual guys any of that
We don't want it to be matching on the the lesser self
the devil, Satan himself, whatever you want to say it, and you know, that's what I tell
people, just make sure you're on the right frequency, the right tune, or else, you know,
you're going to just keep letting the lesser self get the best of you.
And if you want to put it into us, uh-huh. Yeah, if you want to put it to us astrological terms
There's something called the North node and the South node
And so the South node is they kind of like considered your past life where you're coming from it's also considered maybe the lower self
Right, and so it's like the South node is kind of more comfortable to be in it's kind of like the lower frequency of the astrological sign
Whatever sign as long as kind of that the lower frequency of that sign
Then we have something called the North node. That's that's your sign, which is like where you're aspiring and so this
is higher
Higher qualities of these signs right and so it's like so we should always be aspiring to the higher and improving and doing better
And loving more helping you know, it's like it's not gonna be all be love. It's not gonna all be easy
But it will you keep going in that direction and testing effort because it's easier to be in your lower self
And sometimes it is easier. It's just like it's kind of like, you know, we did but we live on earth
We're comfortable here, right and it's like we
We've experienced the human things of pleasure pain hunger and thirst and all these kind of things right and so
You know, so we have these human side, but we also have a spiritual side so we can kind of like
Be both right I can say to you explain who is the most
High is yeah
I can't explain what I think. Yeah. Yeah, the more the most high is God. It's so it's it's you know, it's the one
The one that read it all of this the being the being who so to say brought you to the dance now
Okay, I don't know if I ever got into it with you psyche about what I believe the Bible is
Let me just get this clear nobody's understood the Bible to me is not a religious book
Okay, so let's get religion out of them. So all your churches, I don't believe in this nothing against them
I got nothing against them. I don't believe in religion. So let's get that out of the way
So now I leave it to two to three possible things. It's either a spiritual book
It's either a psychological book or it's either a metaphorical book and where I stand today is I went through
Like I'll still go through that. It's a psychological slash spiritual book
But today, where I'm at, I look at it as just a metaphorical book.
So when I'm reading the story about Adam and Eve, it's not literal, so there's nothing
literal about it.
I don't read it.
I read, I look it in the sense that, for example, this is funny psyche.
The apple is more, you can even look at it as it's about us, truth seekers or conspiracy
theorists or whatever.
Don't, don't eat at this, don't bro, it literally tells you it's the tree of knowledge and good
of good and evil.
Why would any being that created you tell you hey, don't eat from this tree because now you're gonna become like God?
So again, we we we gotta understand that what was really going on what was going on in the garden?
Was it that the creator just created the garden and left and then somehow a
Lesser being got in there like Satan and started giving orders like don't eat at this tree
Hi TG. Oh, yeah, I've heard I've heard a theory about how
you know God created the serpent God knew what the serpent would do God actually created the serpent to
do that because God wanted the matter of the gardens because he wanted them to like you know
it was kind of like that was the the birth process right because they were just they were just immortal
in the garden so once they eat the fruits yeah pregnant basically and then then you know then
you're stuck on the earth right and you're kind of changed to the earth you get another chain on
the earth it's kind of spiritually it's kind of a scary thing like the pregnancy right
but then there are spirit beings that want to be incarnated on the earth, right?
And so there's a big demand for it still, right?
I don't know. I think I would come back, you know, because like it's just boring in the singularity.
The singularity is...
Lonely it's like really it's a you think this is lonely. It's like imagine like
We're here the only only thing that is like you're the if you're all that is everything and so there's nobody else to talk to
Except to yourself
So it's kind of better to split into a billion pieces and like kind of like have your pieces like in the dark about how they're
Are actually like the same being but
Yeah, I don't want to get too deep into it. No, no, no, no for sure
I mean I mean at the end it was funny because I was even just thinking about it like two days ago where I said
We're all a piece to the puzzle right and we're all up to
Try and understand one another rather than you know
So to see rip each other's heads off
Because you know this goes back to the whole thing. I was saying it's easier to judge others than to judge thyself
But yeah, I really, you know, just like what you're saying, obviously it's definitely better to have us, you know, split into billions of other souls than for one big lonely soul.
So I'm definitely with you on that because, you know, I mean, you know, whether people admit it or not, they get lonely.
And then, you know, that's why most people can't really be out of a relationship for too long, right?
You end up brining back to somebody or whatever
You'll even settle back with the people who hurts you just because you can't you can't stand being alone for a little bit
Yeah
And that's like, and then loneliness is part of the human condition because everybody has this longing for connection and coming back together as one, right?
We have this longing for it, but we can never do it, right?
But at least on Earth, right?
Because we are in the duality here, and so we're going to have the dual system here.
Yeah, I think I think and I think if we do we back to the singularity. We'll just get bored again
Let's split up to a billion pieces again. It started all over again
I think that's been going on just for eternity
I think it's as long as we just keep forgetting everything, you know
I think we've lived for probably a long time on on different planes of existence and experience different bodies and all that kind of stuff
Interesting
focus as I'm doing these areas, but yeah it's um what was I gonna say but yeah I
wanted to I wanted to give you my theory there on the garden of Eden and so I
really looked at it from one perspective that it says to not eat from
the tree because so here's
It can go two ways. So I'm gonna tell you this like I became I'm so open-minded to where I'm not gonna sit here and
settle on an absolute truth
Because quite frankly, I don't know how how much these absolute truths exist
Everybody's gonna sit here and tell you know, this is what the verse means then you're gonna have two Protestants contradicting itself
Sorry, actually, I take that back. You're going to have a thousand Protestants contradicting
themselves. You have a thousand Catholics contradicting themselves. You're always going
to have people come. So it's like, you don't actually have an absolute truth. You just
have people in their opinions. And I look at the Garden of Eden, like, psyche, it's
never ending this universe. Everything can be used as a metaphor. Everything can be used
Here's here's I'll just fire off three right off the bat
So don't eat of this tree don't eat of this fruit because surely that's the day you'll die
It's telling you pretty much to not go down the rabbit hole
Because when you do that you're gonna you're gonna physically die like in this reality because now you're spiritually awakened
Right the saying is death and death and the physical is birth in the spiritual and then vice versa
And so it's really telling you, this is just one theory,
don't go down the rabbit hole, be like everybody else,
be stuck in the matrix, be brainwashed,
do what everybody's doing, don't go against the grain,
because when you do all this stuff going against the grain,
that's when you're gonna die, like that's what,
because you know, you're gonna get,
you're gonna get a certain type, see,
what's the same is with this type of,
certain type of intelligence,
it's really gonna make you not even wanna live.
Right and that's why a lot of people get yeah, go ahead. Go ahead. No, but is there is there even
Is there even really a real death?
It's like if we like you know if we die in this earth body and we can and we continue on in the spirit
It's like then the earth body is just like a quick one second of our
Existence of the spiritual being if they can think of that's like pieces like a little our whole life is like a dream
Like it's like a second long, you know, it's just like
Yeah, it's more
So it's like you said, right like to come to earth, right? It's it's just it's an experience, right?
So you're saying like what we're told is pretty much in
virtual
Oh
I'm losing you dude. I can't hear you. Oh gosh my there's something my hair got all knot it up. Oh
Yeah, but then it's interesting. I think she's in palace. Um, thank you
Yeah, I mean I
I am
It's probably insecure. I mean, I think we I think maybe part of being human is like being a little bit like
making sure you're
You know
video ends but but uh
Yeah, oh, I guess you gone, but yeah, I think we're all
We are something we all things we can improve we all we all prove ourselves, right? That's what it really comes down to
Okay, so
You see is by sexual oh, okay
Okay, so I'll try to show you. Oh
Here we go
Hey, thank you, sorry some somebody called and I tried disconnecting the stupid call
But but I worry
Yes, so I was trying to say it yeah in spiritual language, so to say
You know we choose to come to earth to experience this lifetime
And it said that earth is going to be like the toughest task of them all
So when we go back and be with sores, you know, I'm not really sure if it's the astral
Astral realm or if it's another realm where we're there all the time. I'm pretty sure it's the astral realm
Yeah, and um when you're there, you know, you can you get more freedom, right? Like so
Emmys we can we call them meat costumes meat suits that we're in right now. Yeah, yeah meat suits and so
You know
See, we're only going to experience a lot of the pain here if we allow the flesh to be greater than the spirit.
So, you know, anxiety, pain, depression, all that crap.
And so, you know, that's why, like it's important to fast.
When you fast, you get closer to the most high because now you're telling the flesh, you don't have authority over me.
I have authority over you.
That's really the best benefit of fasting.
I do my best to do it every Sunday, specifically on Sundays, just because that's the day that
works the best for me.
But it's just really...
It's just...
Yeah, yeah.
Now, what do you think of the reincarnation and all that?
Where do you stand on it, Ada?
A reincarnation? Well, it's like, it's something that makes sense to me, and it does, like, you know, I said to you a lot of Buddhism, especially Tibetan Buddhism, and they're very into the reincarnation thing, but it's like, because they stay...
Then it's like, you know, we're over like billions and billions and billions of years that we probably have been alive many many times
We've probably been from a flea to a cockroach to probably been every insect in the evolutionary scale
We even go through the evolutionary scale basically as a even as a you know as in this lifetime
We did because we started as kind of like a you know the
The tadpole and stuff like that right and so it's like we even this we go through the hole
because you ever turn into like a little
Mammal and reptile mammal and who's human right and so
You know you you're high when you see everything you say sounds deep. I well
I would you think I think I do I think I don't know I just like I'd like to think about these things
but I
Don't know maybe I am just high
Uh, you agree you love a beloved shiz curvy woman. Yeah, and Nicole Smith was my like my famous
But they were body type right you love tadpoles. Yeah, we started a little tadpole a little sperm as though I sperm as though
Da or was from for sperm as though a little tiny little tadpole and then
We went from one cell to two cells and then just started duplicating duplicating duplicating. Oh, okay. It's okay
I don't know. I always I always take these personally, you know, you know, they so it's just like where I stand that psyche is that
like
We're in this matrix. We get brainwashed and sidetracked
to forget our mission here and why we came here and
It's like I get the game. I understand the game because it's okay. This is how I tell people you're really gonna
You're really gonna make the best that you can in here. Look at it as it's like a Minecraft game and look at it as you're an NPC in the game
You're a non playable character and look at it as you
One day just woke up and realized hey, I'm in a Minecraft game and what the heck's going on
Now most people are not gonna be able to do that and the truth is I'll tell you this right once you get to an awake awakening level
Whenever you talk to people you have to remember when you were sleeping when you were spiritually sleeping and not awakened and
that's exactly their comprehension level, so
You could literally spend a year
Trying to teach somebody about this and it's gonna go through one ear and out the other because they're gonna
They're going to interpret it just like when you're interpreting boring things to them. It's just boring and they're they're not even listening right so ultimately
You know what I always tell people is we can plant
You know let it seeds in people's heads like just let the seeds you leave it alone let it let it
You know grow on its own if they wanted to grow and they want to come back and ask questions
But don't ever force it on people and it's actually very dangerous to try and wake up an NPC because
When when I woke up it wasn't them, right? It wasn't the prettiest thing psyche like I
Went through this phase where I said I was like well, what the fuck is the point of this shit like what why why did he?
Why did it get created this way? I'm like it doesn't make sense. There's
So much confusion and then but here's why I say do not look at the Bible as a religion look at it as
As a spiritual book because it has a lot of answers. So you want to know it says ask and you shall receive
Psychic Jesus was literally preaching the law of attraction and these people don't tell you that they don't tell you the shit in the church
They don't tell you no go go out and and and what do you call it manifest your react?
They don't teach about manifestation
Instead they just teach you how to just worship worship worship and I'm telling you that's not that's I don't believe
That's what the most I want. I I believe he wants a form of acknowledgement. That's like, yeah, you know
The trees didn't just create itself
But I don't think this being wants to be worship
I just think this being wants you to live out your storyline the same way as if it's in a video game
You remember Grand Theft Auto or San Andreas psyche. Did you play that?
Remember, uh, what was the guy's name again the CJ remember CJ the black guy. Yeah, yeah
So if you remember he had a storyline and that storyline you can't really change it that story like if you try
Let's say the the scene where you're on top of the train if you decide to jump off the train you die
So you have to stay and I that's how I take free will I don't really believe in free will
I think if we want to step outside of our lane, outside of our tunnel vision, it gets
ugly.
And then, you know, you go running back to the most high, you go crying, and I'm asking
for forgiveness, but then you got to get back on the lane.
You got to get back, you got to stay on your trip.
My task is different than your sake.
You got you know and you you got a gift that I don't have like you do the terror cards the first time
I met you you read me the terror cards. I that's not my gift. That'll never be my gift
You see what I mean like we all got her but you but you have a gift. Yeah, but we have different gifts. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, exactly
Yeah, and my gift is my the tarot cards is just a part of like my my empathy my intuition like I consider
You know, it's like it's not it's basically a tool I use so like you know kind of sort through those
Feelings because oh, yeah, also you're saying like some of the things we're talking about these are such emotional
Emotional things that people when people get in their emotions about things, right?
We know it their feeties or whatever they get they have emotional thought
They're not they don't look at it things rationally because the emotions hijack the intellects, right?
That's what it always is
We feel them more so they just tend out to us more and then
So it's always a kind of fight between the emotions and the intellect because the intellects is like saying most of them with the emotions
They're saying it's just bullshit, right?
emotions that are gonna believe anything, they're gonna, yeah.
So, try to balance, it's gonna have a good balance
of the intellect and the most, that's in my brain,
the, you know, the scientific and the creative,
like, you know, we're gonna have all of them,
the whole everything, that's just like one side of it, right?
Yeah, well, I've been, I personally have been,
I personally have been,
you know moving away from
Like emotion and one that and I've been I've been gearing more towards the law of detachment
And I've been kind of practicing that for so long because I realized that when you detach
Everything cut like you become a magnet. You see what I'm saying. So when you detach you become a magnet and also
See it's funny. I like this thing. The narrow says
He says it in the movie, he says, he says, um, never get attached to something that you can't walk out on in 30 seconds. If you feel that he coming around the corner, that was in the movie heat and what I like about that is when he says that it's if we're going to get overly attached to anything.
Anything in this life, then it's gonna consume us. It's gonna take over like psyche. You're when you die and I die
You're not taking your money. I'm not taking my you're not taking your cat. You're not taking your your furniture
Right, it's just your soul your soul is gonna go and people don't understand that like in this holographic world
We don't owe any we don't own anything. We're just experiencing life
You see what I'm saying? So we're experiencing all this stuff, but we don't we don't own it
And I'm I'm gonna be damned if I listen. I'll tell you this honest to God, right? I had um, I
was
helping my parents the other day at their house and
Because in mice at my place at my place. I don't have a lot of stuff left. So I had brought
It's like a container bin, you know storage little bin and I put it in their backyard
I forgot it to put in their house. Do you know what was in there psyche?
Well, I had you remember those pelly pelly jackets from back in the 90s
Uh-huh. Yeah. Yeah
Kind of look like what they look like they were they were the leather jackets
They were kind of like like a lot of the rappers were wearing them
They were pretty expensive leather leather like real time like they're heavy. Well, anyways, I had a black one
It was Scarface Tony Montana black one where he was all over and then I had a white one
So how to the exact same jacket one in black one in white leather
And then I had another one. It was the New York City subway map and then I had another fur one
So in total in that it must have been like
Maybe three thousand dollars worth of jackets. So I had I was moving stuff around putting stuff in their backyard some of my
Tools and stuff and I forgot about that
I remember like a couple months goes by and I came by looking and I was like, oh man
I was like, man, I just remembered
I just remembered I forgot that one box. I said you guys have it and
My mom's like what box are you talking about? I'm like the the box. I had a couple jackets
He's like we didn't see any and they don't they don't have cameras. We came to conclusion somebody stole it
Somebody stole the jackets
But my point is yeah for a second
For a second. I was like, oh fuck man, you know, like those were really cool jackets
But then I remembered I said well wait a sec. You need to practice what you preach man
You'd be like, you know, virtually where you're at here
You don't care for possessions and then I said it is what it is and who cares right? I left it alone
But yeah, I mean that's um
That's just where I stand now with all these earthly things worldly things possessions
And it's like the devil tarot card is like it's kind of that exact exact message of like
the uh, the devil is like basically the earth we chain ourselves voluntarily to it and we know basically feed off of it and
And you know and it's like then the earth is this big one being but it's both male female
Because the most male females are on the earth. It's always like, you know, it's yeah pretty interesting, right?
but wait, wait, wait, wait, so uh,
Hell, yeah, so are you guys a good news? Yeah. Yeah
What do they say? I mean, yeah
What are your troll babies? Thank you. Thank you. You think you can do that going for do you think you can call the chat troll babies?
Can you do that? Well, maybe maybe I mean I have a long troll baby. I have a song called that
trolls make the world go around
Well, they they definitely they definitely make our YouTube world go around right like the trolls are needed
You know, yeah, the trolls are definitely need they they don't even know how much I love them. They don't know how much
cockroaches are needed so like you know
So there's reasons for anybody, right?
That's fucking hilarious man
That's what you see. Here's what the trolls need to know when you're talking to a veteran
Who's been on here since the day YouTube opened up?
Right like early. It was technically oh three
I think of 04 when YouTube opened up when someone's been on here right now for that long bro a
Troll bit a troll baby like coming at somebody like me like it's like
You know, you're throwing a thousand fucking pillow fisted punches that are just doing nothing
That are absolutely doing nothing, you know, I'm saying easy work
Easy work
What's that bro
You got a troll baby trying to get on
Who the fuck's this
Speak
This guy goes by the name of I'm tired I he starred but he's clicking the link though
So he's professional at this what he's doing now. Oh lord. Oh
Irby's the number one Irby's the number who's number two we got sassy
lava number three
Sorry
Who was who is this who's I'm tired. Oh, that's that's that's that's uh, that's uh, rando rando rondo
Yeah
Hey rondo, how are you today?
If you're there, who's the JT troll by the way, this is a JT troll. Oh
Let's play on the picture. Hold on. There's a JT fella in the chat. Who's that role?
Okay, it's not a form ball. JT is the wolf man. He's a woman in rain. He's like a
He's a nice person. He's got a
cross side. Why is he? Why is
he a cross side troll? I don't
know. What do you got cross
sides? Did he get cross side?
It looks like he's got a
cross side. That's what I look
for. Let me see. Hey, Barry,
Barry, you're going to have to
donate, bro. You're going to
have to donate to get somebody
Yeah, I don't mind. She's like you like it's kind of cool and work together, right?
Well, well, I know you're trolling to giving you money to get me off
But it's like there's no, you know, there's it's not personal though
Like I help you get money, right? That's a cool idea. I'll piss off some of these trolls so you donate
They donate for me. I love it. Thank you. Appreciate that. Oh, absolutely, bro. I've done stuff like that
Very it's kind of hard to prove your point when I've doubled the numbers for I
Doubled the number since I came in here bro. It's hard to say this guy's putting anybody to see
The cross a troll that's a good name
Yes, are you there? Yeah, it's me. It's me. I'm listening what y'all saying
Okay, okay, I'm making sure you're the right person
Yes, yes, let me ask you this bro. Where do you get off taking LES his name, bro?
What's the problem with his name?
No, because the producer
And you do it at the same way he does you're putting the dot in between the e and the s
Can't be a problem. I'm not being honest. I'm from the lower. I'm the real alias from the lower
No, you're not. No, you're not. Where the real alias from what what borrow?
alias passed away, right? No, he's still alive
No, he hasn't he's from the bridge. He's from Queensbridge. He's still alive and well man. Yeah, he's from Kingsbridge
That's not alias. No, I said Queensbridge
I said Queensbridge not King's bridge. That's what I said Queensbridge. I thought you said Kings muffler. I said Queensbridge
He didn't pass away though. He's still alive. Well, I told me he passed away. Oh
So now you try to take his name cuz he passed away. No, no
Queens Queens is not from the low east side. No, I know I know you from you from my man. Hi, man. Yeah, that's the lower east side
That's LDS
Hello, what's that? Oh, okay. Now I see why use Ellie. Yeah. Okay. Okay. I got you. I got you know
I mean, it's not I'm not trying to take nobody's name. It's um, this is where I'm from
Yeah
Yeah, they told me that um, I went to Dave some guy named Dave some arm show on one of the YouTube things some panel
And he got his panel got deleted. You know me, but he was the arm
The arm he told me I was passed away
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the true LES did pass away.
No, he didn't.
He's still alive.
But you don't know your hip hop.
You don't know your hip hop.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You don't know your hip-hop bro. What can you tell him about you being around since the conception that you took?
You don't know your hip-hop bro. You don't know your hip-hop bro.
Go back and watch the documentaries bro.
Go back and watch the hip-hop documentaries bro.
Go back and watch. No he didn't bro. Where you guys getting this from?
I was fucking mental. I was just kidding bro.
No he did not bro. Where you getting your input from?
No he did not.
Yeah
This motherfucker, what you mean where I'm getting my info
Are you getting it from WWE bootleg calm where you get it from man?
Okay, okay, let's see if you really know LES hold on let me ask him this question
Let me ask him this question on Nasr's
Elmatic what what song did he produce?
No, we ain't talking about music
I'll give you a hand. I'll give you a life
I'll give you a hand the song is called life's all be be what?
Life's a what?
Retard, okay, life's a bit life's a bit. That's the song that's the song that any has produced, okay?
I
Thank you
Sky dummy, bro. Sky. I don't know his hip-hop. He coming here to troll me
We're talking about the original LES dreamers. No, there's no there's only one LES and he's a producer. I don't care about your streamer
Don't cover your streamer, bro
Guys balls whoever you're talking about
I'm uh, I'm psyche's right-hand man. Who are you bro? Oh, you are here
Oh
Are you the guy that kicks out your mouth?
No, no, no, no, no, I just listened somebody was trying to get me
They were trying to they were trying to get me out they're trying to get me out and I don't mind getting psyche some money to get me kicked out
How many New Yorkers how many New Yorkers how many New Yorkers are on the panel right now?
How many New Yorkers
One of you that went one you slept up on but me. I'm a public figure. You know how many New Yorkers
What's up?
How many new yorkers is on the panel right now?
How many new yorkers is on the panel right now? Where's it? Where's alexander?
Where's alexander we're missing alexander, dude, you're boring everybody to tears man read the roof
Born people
Another two people are doing right now, and you and you over here over talking
We're fucking from New York you fucking dick. Well, it's not all of you dick. I only hear about two actions. So who's from New York here?
Your mama
Go relax man. It's a simple question. I don't know why you're getting all in here like you're like a pseudo Christian
Self-reflecting guru or what you what you do? No, I'm just I'm just a normal guy. Where are you, bro?
Man listen the devil
Why are these people are in their feet?
Well, why are you guys just tampon bleeding bro? Why are you guys just tampon bleeding man? Why are you tampon bleeding, right?
But Jesus
So you couldn't fully commit to Christianity so you like you combined it with like new age shit that basically what happened or
Define Christianity, let's see if you can define Christianity
Oh my god
The fund is page the fund is your mother fucker
Define Christianity, let's go the fund Internet
Quick run, pushy, quick run, bury the pushy, bury the pushy, bury the faggot, bury the faggot, bury the faggot.
You're using words you don't even know
Hey, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the bearer, let's bury the
I can't say maggot, you can't say maggot, you can't say maggot